“Ienai” mama de ii no?
Is it ok to keep not saying it?
Senaka awase takane no hane
Back to back, wings aloft.
Chikai you de tooi kimi ni
You seem close and yet you are so far away.
Itsu no hi ka osero mitai
As with Othello,
Umetsuku sareteku kokoro
our hearts fill up in everyday life.
Shinzou no neiro
It doesn't matter, if you can't
quite stand by your feelings.
Sukoshi damattetemo ii yo
Karisome janai zero kyori ni~
We are so close,
hardly a leaf fits between us
Tsuyogatte miseta
and you overplayed it.
Waratta furi no kimi ni
I wonder what else I can expect
from you, faking a smile?
Nani ga dekiru ka na~
Kimochi no tsuuchi ofu ni shita mama
Is it okay to continue not saying it,
“ienai” mama de ii no~?
as long as my
feelings notification stays off?
Mikansei na koi demo ii kara
If a less than perfect love is enough for you,
let me save the seat next to you.
Yume wa kimi to misasete yo
Soba ni itai… dake nante sa
I want to be by your side,
but for some reason
Ienai, ienai, ienai~
I can't bring myself to say it,
can't bring myself to say it, can't bring myself to say it.
Fukanzen na boku demo ii nara
Even an unfinished love is enough for me,
Tonari wa yoyaku sasete yo
let me be by your side.
Kimi ga ii… mata ienai
I want you, but I can't bring myself to say it,
Kowashitakunai kara sa~
because I don't want to break it.
Dakara ima wa
Therefore, it's okay to keep not saying it.
“iwanai” mama de ii no.