nee nee
Look, look,
nanika iou ni mo kotoba tarazu da
I don’t have the words to say anything
aita kuchi ga fusagaranai kara kara
Because, because I’ve been left open-mouthed
nee nee
Look, look,
damarikokutte mo kotoba irazu da
Even if I stay silent, words aren’t necessary
me tte mono o iu kara
Because my eyes will speak for me
wasurete iku koto wa mushi ga tabehajimeta kekka da
Forgetting is a fruit that bugs have begun to eat
omoide no naka ja itsumo waratte’ru kao na dake
All that remains in my memory is an always-smiling face
yuugureta iro sora o tonde
As I’m flying through the twilight-colored sky,
kono mama taiki sae tobidashite
Even shooting through the atmosphere,
mashita, shidai ni chiisaku natte’ku no wa
Below me, rapidly growing small,
kimi no ita machi da
Is the town where you were
kutsu no saki ni hana ga saita
Beneath my shoes, flowers bloomed
ooki na hi no hana ga saita
Giant flowers of fire bloomed
kokorogoto nokoshite yukou, da nante omou
“I’ll leave behind everything that’s in my heart,” I think
sonna natsu ga mieta
That’s the kind of summer I could see
nee nee
Look, look,
kimi o shirou ni mo docchi tsukazu da
Even if I try to get to know you, it’s ambiguous
kitto hana ni kakeru kara
Because you’re full of pride
seisei suru koto nante nan ni mo nai kedo
There’s nothing that can make me feel refreshed
kyou mo sora ga kirei da naa
But the sky is beautiful again today
boku no tabeta mono subete ga kitto sei e no taika da
I’m sure that everything I’ve eaten is a compensation paid to life
imasara na boku wa YODAKA ni sae mo nare ya shinai
I’m too late, and now I can’t even become a nighthawk
asayaketa iro sora o matte
Dancing in the dawn-colored sky
nani o negau ka nante gumon da
“What do you wish for?” is such a foolish question
otona ni natte wasurete ita
I grew up and forgot about it
kimi o utsusu me ga jama da
That you’re reflected in my eyes is such a nuisance
zutto shita de hana ga natta
Flowers were always ringing out beneath me
ooki na hi no hana ga natta
Giant flowers of fire were ringing out
oto dake demo naite shimau, da nante omou
“The noise alone makes me cry,” I think
sonna natsu o kiita
That’s the kind of summer I heard
nee nee
Look, look,
sora o tobou ni mo owari shirazu da
Even if I fly in the sky, there’s no end to it
kitto kimi o sagashite shimau kara kara
Because I’ll surely end up searching for you
yuugureta iro sora o tonde
As I’m flying in the twilight-colored sky,
kono hoshi no ima sae nukedashite
Breaking free of even the present of this planet,
mashita, shidai ni chiisakute
Below me, rapidly growing small
kieta no wa kimi no ita machi da
And then disappearing, is the town where you were
natsu no sora ni hana ga saita
In the summer sky, flowers bloomed
ooki na hi no hana ga saita
Giant flowers of fire bloomed
itsu made demo naite itai, da nante omou
“I want to keep crying forever,” I think
sonna natsu ga kieta
That’s the kind of summer that vanished