last ikuyo
Let's go, one more time!
Kizuna Music♪
"Kizuna Music♪"
kyoushitsu no mado no soto hashagu koe
Cheery voices outside the classroom window
komorebi wa kirakira furisosoide
Sunshine piercing brightly through the trees
mainichi ga tokubetsu datta basho ni
The place where every day felt special
minna mata atsumatteta
All of us gathered there again
watashitachi ga tsunagatteru imi
There's a reason we're all together
tabun… guuzen janai
I don't think… it's a coincidence
datte oto wo awasetara
Cause when our sounds blend together…
Kizuna Myuujikku♪
Bounding Music♪
tada hitamuki ni oikakete ita
We'd been chasing it single-mindedly
mune no oku no omoi
The feelings deep in our hearts
kizuitara
When we discover them
(minna de)
(Together)
chizu wo hirogete
Let's spread open the map
kibou no michi wo jiguzagu susumou!
And zig-zag forward on the road to our dreams!
Kizuna Myuujikku♪
Bonding Music♪
daisukina uta
A song we love,
yakusoku no uta
A song of promise,
eien no uta
A song everlasting
todokeyou!
Let it reach!
watashitachi itsudatte
For now and always
seiippai! forever for dreaming!
With all our might! Forever for dreaming!
yume no mukou e~
To where dreams come true…
deatta toki no koto oboeteiru?
Do you remember when we first met?
afuredasu omoi hibikiau yume
Hearts full of hope and dreams aligned
kizuitara kizutsuite kizutsukete
Before we knew it, we hurt each other
kizuna mata fukamatteta
But we grew even closer in the end
gonin dake ga shitteiru koto tabun
There are stories only the five of us know
…sugu omoidasu
A few… probably spring to mind
uta ga oshiete kureru yo
Our songs teach me the important things
Kizuna Myuujikku♪
Bonding Music♪
ano hashi watari
I crossed the bridge
ano oka wo koe
And climbed over the hill
sono kabe wo koetara
As I leapt beyond the wall
kimi ga ita
You were waiting for me
(aeta ne)
(We met at last)
hyoushiki no nai
I can journey throught this maze
mayoi no michi mo kimi to nara ikeru
With no end in sight as long as I'm with you
Kizuna Myuujikku♪
Bonding Music♪
taisetsuna uta
A precious song,
seishun no uta
A song of youth,
hajimari no uta
A song of beginnings
kanadeyou!
Let's play it!
nandodemo itsumade mo
Over and over, boundless
seiippai! forever for dreaming!
With all our might! Forever for dreaming!
uta wo shinjiru~
I believe in our song
kyou wa honto ni kiite kurete arigatou
Thank you so much for being here tonight!
saigo zenryouku de ikou
Let's give it all we've got 'til the very end!
hai hai hai hai
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
itsuka omoide ni kawatta toki
Someday, when our adventures turn into memories
kono uta wo kiita nara
If we listen to this song
donna koto wo kanjiru kana?
What do you think we'll feel?
itoshikute yasashiku
Sweet and sentimental,
ureshikute setsunakatta
Overjoyed and heartbroken
omoi subete dakishime~
Embrace them all with open arms
Kizuna Myuujikku♪
Bonding Music♪
kokoro furuete
Overwhelmed by emotion,
yuuki afurete
Swelling with courage
namida ga dechaisou
On the verge of tears,
utaou yo
Let's sing together
(minna de)
(All of us)
koe takaraka ni
With our voices loud
ashita no uta wo
A song of tomorrow!
mirai e no uta wo!
A song leading to the future!
sonna…
That's our…
myuujikku♪
Music♪
daisukina uta
A song we love,
yakusoku no uta
A song of promise,
eien no uta
A song everlasting
todokeyou!
Let it reach!
watashitachi itsudatte
For now and always
seiippai! forever for dreaming!
With all our might! Forever for dreaming!
kimi to issho dayo
I'm right by your side
forever for dreaming!
Forever for dreaming!
kimi wo shinjiru~
I believe in you