Yokaze
akiramereba raku datta
If I had given up, it would have been easier,
ikutsu mo no koukai o
But I've wrapped myself in countless regrets.
matoinagara usuyami
In the faint darkness, I lurk,
hisomi ashi ni makaseru
Leaving my steps to wander on their own.
hyururi kami o tokasu
A cold wind gently combs my hair,
tsumetai kaze dake ga
boku no katachi o shitteru~
It’s the only thing that knows my shape.
sonna yoru ga~
Nights like these...
shizuka ni kakushite kureru kara
Quietly conceal me,
boku no iro mo wasurete
Erasing even the hues of myself.
karamitsuita mama no kage sae
Even the shadows clinging tightly to me
atokatanaku tsutsunde'ku
Are completely enveloped, leaving no trace.
yoru ga subete aa~ someru~
The night, ah, it dyes everything.
kikonasenai tadashisa ya
The righteousness I can't wear properly,
iiyodonda hontou mo
And the truths I hesitate to say aloud—
nani mo sute kire nakute
I couldn’t abandon any of them.
chittomo kawareya shinakatta~
I couldn’t change at all.
hikikaese mo shinakute
I couldn't turn back, either,
ippou tsuukou no
Carrying these helpless, one-way feelings
subenai omoi o~
hitoribocchi no hate made
All the way to the lonely end.
mochitsuzuketa no nara
If I did, would I be forgiven?
yurusareru no kana~
hitoiki goto koku naru yami ni
With each breath, the darkness grows deeper,
jiwari jiwari najindeku
Gradually, gradually, I blend into it.
gaado reeru mo hodoukyou mo
The guardrails, the pedestrian bridges,
onaji yoru ni tokeru~ tokeru~
All dissolve into the same night, fading away.
shizuka ni kakushite kureru kara
Quietly conceal me,
boku no iro mo wasurete
Erasing even the hues of myself.
kaze ni yurareru jiyuu no naka
In the freedom of being swayed by the wind,
hitorigochita wazurai mo
Even the murmurs of my troubles—
yoru ga subete aa~ someru~
The night, ah, it dyes everything.