Kimi no Hitomi o Meguru Bouken
(The Adventure Encircling Your Eyes)
Aqours
Composed by: Watanabe Kazunori
Arranged by: Watanabe Kazunori
Lyrics by: Hata Aki
nazo wa nazo wa itsumo me no mae de chigau basho o hiraku~
Mysteries, they always open doors to someplace else right in front of your eyes
nazo o nazo o hodoite kono sekai de asobou yo~
So solve the mystery, and enjoy yourself in this world
Escape and Search on mind
negai tozashicha susumenai hazukashigarazu kite yo
Locking your desires in your heart won't get you anywhere, so come along, cast aside your shame
hitori ja mienai tegakari
Those clues that you can't see when you're alone
issho naraba wakaru wakaru
We'll be able to understand them when we're together
kurayami terasu you ni koe kimi ni todoke to yonde miru
To bring light to the darkness, I try calling out to you
tsunagaru hazu to shinjitara kiseki no you na hikari de
If we believe that we're connected, a miraculous light will...
bokutachi wa meguri au ne
We'll finally meet each other
mune ga atsuku naru yo~!
That really gets me excited!
boku wa kimi o miteru kimi no me ni boku o utsushite yo~
When I look at you, your eyes reflect my silhouette
"sagashite" to kokoro ga ooki na kodou todoketagaru~
The thumping of my heart calls out, begging you to find me
nazo ga nazo ga motto tokimeki e to kawaru you ni~
To turn these mysteries into some form of excitement
Escape and Search on mind
geemu ga hajimaru nozonda sono toki
When you desire for the games to begin
mekurumeku mirai nozonda sono toki
When you desire a dazzling future
bouken to yonde ii yo koi mitai ni
It's alright to call it an adventure; it's just like love
ima tomaranai jetto kousutaa no suriru
You'll experience the thrill of a roller coaster in your heart
kurayami koso hontou no koto ga
I truly believe that only darkness
ukabiagaru to omounda~
Can surface the truth
tsunagaru hazu to shinjiru yo kiseki no you na hikari ga
If we believe that we're connected, a miraculous light will...
bokutachi o maneki kotae no chikaku ni iru yotte
It calls out to us, telling us that we're so close to the answer
kanjisasete kureru no wa honnou teki na mono sa~
Being able to feel something like that is just instinctive
sara ni... atsuku!
To become even more passionate!
nazo wa nazo wa itsumo me no mae de chigau basho o hiraku~
Mysteries, they always open doors to someplace else right in front of your eyes
"mitsuketa" no kotoba o matteru yo hayaku sagashite yo~
I await you with the words “You found me!” on the corners of my lips, so find me quick
nazo o nazo o hodoite kono sekai de asobou yo~
Solve the mystery, and enjoy yourself in this world
shiranai koto ga ippai de~
There are so many things that we do not yet know
soredemo saki e susumou yo~
Even so, move forward, charge ahead!
tashikamenakucha nani mo kawaranai~ kara~
Nothing will ever change if you don't see it for yourself
nazo o nazo o hodokeba
Once you solve the mystery
hitori janai yo ne~
I'll no longer be alone... Right?
hitori janai
(You're not alone)
boku wa kimi o miteru kimi no me ni boku o utsushite yo~
When I look at you, your eyes reflect my silhouette
"sagashite" to kokoro ga ooki na kodou todoketagaru~
The thumping of my heart calls out, begging you to find me
nazo ga nazo ga motto tokimeki e to kawaru you ni~ asobou yo~
To turn these mysteries into some form of excitement, let's play!
Escape and Search on mind