Te to te o tsunaide
kimi to issho ni niji no saki e~
Let's hold hands together
with you beyond the rainbow
Takaramono o mitsuke ni
DOA no mukou e dekakeyou
Let's go out the door to find the treasure
GARASU no kutsu mo basho mo
nai kedo jitto shiterarenai
There's no place to put on
these glass slippers, but we can't sit still
Tokimeki no oto takanaru
kodou no hari CHIKKUTAKKU
The sound of a heartbeat rings out,
the beating needle goes tick-tock
Mahou no jumon wa kokoro ga shitteru
Our hearts know the magic spell
Wakuwaku hibiku MERODI~ kikoeru?
Mimi o sumashite
Can you hear that exciting,
resounding melody? Listen closely
Hajimaru! Minna de "SUTAATO!"
hashiridasou Let's go!!
It begins! Let's all start
running at "start!" Let's go!!
Asa da yo ohayou! Asobou!
It's morning, good morning! Let's play!
Sora ni egaku yume wa
taiyou yori mo mabushiku kagayaiteru
The dreams we draw in the sky
are more dazzling than the sun
Genki ni utaou! Odorou!
Let's sing and dance! Cheerfully!
Sekaijuu ni todoke mirai o terasu
hikari ni naru yo watashi-tachi~
Delivered around the world, we'll turn
into light that illuminates the future
Te to te o tsunaide
kimi to issho ni niji no saki e
Let's hold hands together
with you beyond the rainbow
Kanaeru no kiseki sae~
kirakira ni Shine In The Sky~
We'll make it come true,
even miracles sparkle, shine in the sky☆