Dreamy Aqours color...
Kyou wa kyou no kibun de tondeku yo
Today, I'll fly over, depending on how I feel
Ima o shikkari to kanjitai~
I want to really feel the present
Kono shunkan o ikite sukitooru aozora miwataseba
Live in this moment; just looking across the clear, blue sky
Itsudatte shiawase da yo~
I'll always be happy
Aa kaze no muki wa kawatteku kedo~
Ah, although the wind's direction will change
Yume ou jounetsu wa kawaranai kara~
The passion for my dreams won't change
(Your go!)
Iki ga kirete mo mada hashirou ikeru, ikeru yo!
I'll still run, even when I'm out of breath - I can do it, I can do it!
Nemuru chikara yobisamasou~
I'll wake up the strength resting inside
Hajimarunda hajimarunda hajimetaku nattara~
It's starting, it's starting, once you want to start something
Umarerunda umarerunda atarashii tokimeki~
That's the moment, that's when it's born - a new excitement
Kinou made~ nakatta mono ga~ fui ni~ arawarete ugokidasu~
It didn't exist yesterday, but it appeared suddenly, and started moving
Hajimarunda hajimarunda hajimetaku nattara~
It's starting, it's starting, once you want to start something
Umarerunda umarerunda atarashii tokimeki~ e to~
That's the moment, that's when it's born - a new excitement
Te o nobasu kimi ga suki nanda~
You stretch out your hands, I like that about you
Tanoshinjaeba nandemo ari da to~
As long as we're having fun, anything goes
Saa, tobidase~!
Come on, let's fly!
Sekai wa itsudatte mawatteru
The world is always turning
Dakara bokura no keshiki mo henka shite
That's why the scenery we see changes
Kono shunkan mo itsuka omoide ni naru no~?
At some point, this moment will also become a memory
Aozora mo yuuyake asayake e to~
And the blue sky, a sunset, and then a sunrise
Aa kaze no iro ga kawatteku yo ne~
Ah, there'll be a different color to the wind, won't there?
Tonari de mitetara setsunaku natte sa~
I was next to you, and I looked over and felt sad
(Your smile!)
Me ga attara tonikaku waraou
Then our eyes met, for now I'll just smile
Sore de kieru yo
With that, my sadness disappears
Sabishisa nante kiechau yo~
My loneliness disappears
Omoshiroinda omoshiroinda hajimete no koto ga~
It's fun, it's fun, the first time doing something
Hikarerunda hikarerunda atarashii chousen ni wa~
It's drawing me, drawing me, a new challenge
Nando mo deatte mitai~
I want to meet this feeling, over and over
Motto~ tooku e ikitai no sa~
I want to go further and further
Issho ni ne~!
Together, of course!
Mirai no iro ga~ kawaru~ kawatte mo kitto~
The color of the future keeps changing, however,
Bokura no omoi wa~ kawaranai
Our feelings will never change, I want to show them to you
Tsutaetai~ omoi ga aru~ zutto arunda yo~
They're here, and they'll always stay here
Tsutawatteru to shinjitai
I believe that I've expressed them to you
Datte~ kimi no koe ga~ kikoete kuru kara~
Because I can hear your voice
Mune ni kimi no koe ga todoku yo...
Your song has reached my heart...
Hajimarunda hajimarunda hajimetaku nattara~
It's starting, it's starting, once you want to start something
Umarerunda umarerunda atarashii tokimeki~
That's the moment, that's when it's born - a new excitement
Kinou made~ nakatta mono ga~ fui ni~ arawarete ugokidasu~
It didn't exist yesterday, but it appeared suddenly, and started moving
Hajimarunda hajimarunda hajimetaku nattara~
It's starting, it's starting, once you want to start something
Umarerunda umarerunda atarashii tokimeki~ e to~
That's the moment, that's when it's born - a new excitement
Te o nobasu kimi ga suki nanda~
You stretch out your hands, I like that about you
Tanoshinjaeba nandemo ari da to~
As long as we're having fun, anything goes
Saa, tobidase~!
Come on, let's fly!
Ganbacchau kokoro tte donna iro darou?
What color do our souls take on when we give our all?
Yumemiru bokura tte donna iro darou?
What color do we take on when we dream?
Ganbacchau kokoro tte donna iro darou?
What color do our souls take on when we give our all?
Yumemiru bokura tte donna iro darou?
What color do we take on when we dream?