tadayotte kieta nichijou wa
Our daily lives are drifting away.
marude genjitsukan no nai yume no you de
This feels like an unrealistic dream.
wakaranai kotoga wakaranai kodomo no youna boku wo
I don't get this. I don't understand, I'm like a child;
oboresou na koe de yondeiru
As we call to the drowning voices.
(Why did you call me Crying Crying Crying ?)
okubyou nano wa onaji hazu nano ni
Even though we are just as timid,
(He can't understand, has not need it)
uketometai to konna ni mo negau no wa
I want to accept it, even though I wish for it this much.
kokoro no kara o sukitooru sakebi o
The emptiness of my heart and my crystal clear scream.
tsukisasu hahen o nijimu honne o
The piercing pieces and my seeping true feelings:
terashidashita hitotsu hitotsu taisetsu na anata da to
All of these are reflected one by one.
You are the most important person to me.
shitte hoshii kara shitteita kara
Because I want you to know. Because I already knew.
(What a beautiful color)