koko wa uchi no mura
Here is my village
nodoka no dokoro non
A peaceful place
demo
uchi wa doki doki kyou mo non!
But
I'm excited today too!
yappari koko tte inaka nanon?
After all, this is the countryside?
(he?)
inaka ni sunderu?
(Hmm?)
Are we living in the countryside?
ijiketenai non
I am not shy...
Nattsun,
Hotarun,
Koma-chan wa?
(jii)
What about Koma-chan?
ame okure
(Stare...)
Give me candy!
wara wasete kureru..
She is making me laugh
(sei!)
uchi ima kameraman
(Yei!)
Now I'm the photographer.
oh, kyamera!
Oh, camera!
(ha!)
ne, ne, kocchi ni ii mono aru non
(Ha!)
Hey, hey, I found something cool over there!
neko jarashi
Cat's tail
(ha!)
neko jarashi
(Ha!)
Cat's tail
(ho!)
uchi mo jaretsuku neko jarashi
(Ho!)
I'm playing with a cat's tail
(ha!)
kyou wa arigatou
(Ha!)
Thank you for today
arigatou nan
Thanks to you, too
ashita mo asoberu?
Can we also play tomorrow?
asoberun
hontou?!
Yes we can
Honoka-chin ikutsu nanon?
Really?!
How old are you Honoka?
shougaku ichinen
First-grader in elementary school
uchi to issho nanon
I'm also in first grade!
onaji da ne!
shinkansen
So we're the same!
Bullet train
ano nagai yatsu!?
The long one!?
(sou!)
huh yappa Tokai sugoi non na..
(Exactly!)
Huh Tokai is pretty cool after all
(ara)
goro goro
(Ara)
o-juusu ima jiru ko matsuna
Rumble rumble
Would you like some juice?
hourensouji sho furida
(somethingsomething)
hajimete mita
First time I've seen that.
(pasu!)
konai no?
(Pasu!)
dame nano?
Can't you come?
sou nano?
Is it bad?
nan nano?
Is that so?
koitsu no namae wa
What is that?
I will call this guy "Oshio"
oshio ni suru non
nya..
Nya..
nya...
nya!
Nya!
yappari koko tte inaka nanon?
After all, this is the countryside?
(he?)
inaka ni sunderu?
(Hmm?)
Are we living in the countryside?
ijiketenai non
I am not shy...
Nattsun,
Hotarun,
Koma-chan wa?
(jii)
What about Koma-chan?
ame okure
(Stare...)
Give me candy!
wara wasete kureru..
She is making me laugh
(sei!)
uchi ima kameraman
(Yei!)
Now I'm the photographer.
oh, kyamera!
Oh, camera!
(ha!)
ne, ne, kocchi ni ii mono aru non!
(Ha!)
Hey, hey, I found something cool over there!
neko jarashi
Cat's tail
(ha!)
neko jarashi
(Ha!)
Cat's tail
(ho!)
uchi mo jaretsuku neko jarashi
(Ho!)
I'm playing with a cat's tail
(ha!)
(Ha!)