I spent all night thinking about my reason
for playing in this band now.
We're Kessoku Band.
We're going to play our song,
"Guitar, Solitude, and the Blue Planet"!
I do still want to become popular
and have everyone go crazy for me...
But now... it's not just for me.
It's the four of us!
totsuzen furu yuudachi aa
A sudden evening shower falls
kasa mo nai ya iya
And yeah, it figures,
I don't have an umbrella...
sora no go kigen nanka shiranai
Who cares how the sky's feeling, anyway?
kisetsu no kawarime no fuku wa
When it's time for the seasons to change
I never figured out what
it means to have "growth."
nani kirya iin daro
What are you supposed to wear? Who knows?
haru to aki doko icchattan da yo
Spring and fall... yeah, where'd they go?
But right now, what I want
is to stay with this band and
have people go crazy for us!
iki mo dekinai
The pressure of information, suffocating
jouhou no atsuryoku
memai no rasen da
A spiral of vertigo
I want to make Nijika-chan's
actual dream come true.
watashi wa doko ni iru
Don't know where I am
konna ni konna ni
I can hear myself breathing
so loud, so loud...
So... I can't afford to blow this audition!
iki no oto ga suru no ni
hen da ne sekai no oto ga
But why? I can't hear the
sounds of the world...
I don't want the band to end just yet!
shinai
tarinai tarinai dare ni mo kizukarenai
It's not enough, not enough,
No one knows I'm here
nagurigaki mitai na oto dasenai joutai de sakenda yo
I screamed when I couldn't
make a scribble of a sound
ari no mama nante dare ni miserun da
Who am I supposed to show "just who I am" to?
baka na watashi wa utau dake
So I'm singing just like the fool I am
buchimakechaou ka hoshi ni
Let's lay it all out to the stars!