hanasaku ya akara hiku hoho ni~
Blossoms bloom, on your rosy cheeks
sazanami yoru wa umi
Wavelets of the sea nigh
anata wa mizugiwa hitori hohoemu dake
You are smiling by the shore alone
ima, omoide ni boku wa~ miyako ochi
Now, in memories I am leaving the capital
hanauta, kirei da ne
Beautiful, these hums of yours
asu ni wa yukun da ze
We are heading towards tomorrow
umineko ga naita ne
The seagulls cried
tori demo nakun da ne
So birds cry too, huh
kokoronashi kawaitara wakare no jikan da ze
When the tears dry before long, it’s time to say goodbye
natsukaze momarete anata ni asai kage
Stirred by summer winds, light shadows on you
sarari hanasaku ya akara hiku hoho ni~
Swiftly blossoms bloom, on your rosy cheeks
sazanami, yoru wa umi
Wavelets of the sea at night
anata wa mizugiwa hitori te wo furu dake
You are waving by the shore alone
ima, omoide ni boku wa~ miyako ochi
Now, in memories I am leaving the capital
asayake, kirei da ne
Beautiful, glow of the sunrise
fune wa mou tatsun da ze
Already the boat has set sail
umineko ga naita ne
The seagulls cried
anata mo nakun da ne
So you’re crying too, huh
hitozato hanarete naru oto wa mukai nami
Away from the world, splash of the head sea
tobu tori wa tooku e asu kara mukou made
Birds soaring afar, to the future beyond tomorrow
mizu ni ochi nagare yagate uki
Glide into the water, at last all is woe
anata ni kogareru fune wa umi
Boat of your yearning at sea
oshimikaku yubi wa omou take bakari~
Fingers that speak remorse are the whole of my heart
chiru omoide wa nami ka~ miyako ochi
Aren’t these falling memories like waves? Leaving the capital
miyako hanarete fune susumu
Away from the capital, the boat heads on
mizu wa nagarete toki mo mata
Water flows, so does time
boku wa anata no omoide ni
I am in your memories
tada no kioku ni
In your mere recollection
kou raku wa akara hiku hoho no~
Enamoured of your rosy cheeks
yosekiyu nami no hana
Foam of the sea nigh
anata wa mizugiwa hitori hohoemu dake
You are smiling by the shore alone
ima, omoide ni boku wa~
Now, in memories I am
sarari hanasaku ya akara hiku hoho ni~
Swiftly blossoms bloom, on your rosy cheeks
sazanami, yoru wa umi
Wavelets of the sea at night
anata wa mizugiwa hitori te wo furu dake
You are waving by the shore alone
ima, sayou nara boku wa~ miyako ochi
Now, farewell, I am leaving the capital