But...
I refuse to let it stay this way!
ano BAND no uta ga watashi ni wa
That band's songs sound to me
kandakaku hibiku waraigoe ni kikoeru
like shrill laughter all around
ano BAND no uta ga watashi ni wa
That band's songs are to me
tsunzaku
like the piercing clang of a railway crossing
fumikiri no oto mitai
senaka wo
Don't push me forward
osunayo
mou soko ni ressha ga kuru
There's a train coming
me wo tojiru
I close my eyes
kurayami ni sasu gokou
There's a halo in the darkness
mimi fusagu
I cover my ears
tashika ni kizamu kodou
There's a steady beating pulse within
mune no oku
Deep in my chest
mi wo yurasu shinzou
My heart makes my body sway
hoka ni nani mo kikitakunai
I don't want to hear anything else
watashi ga hanatsu
Nothing but the sounds I'm making
oto igai