hi ga ochite utagoe wa hoshi to nari~
The sun goes down, and the voice becomes a star
nagaredasu Time Lapse
Flowing like a Time Lapse
sou kanjitsuzukeru~
Yes, I still feel it
wo~ wo~ wo~wo~
"tomare" no sain ga~ jirettai jirettai
Stop signs make me so impatient, so impatient
kanjou no supiido ga~ kanetsu suru kanetsu suru
My emotional engine keeps overheating, overheating
kono hen de shoukyuushi kana?~ sonna himanai to~
Do I take a short break now? I don't have time for that
yumemiru haato ga~ kasoku suru kasoku suru
My dreaming heart keeps accelerating, accelerating
wo~ wo~
Time Lapse starry sky~
Time Lapse starry sky
hoshi wa mawaritsuzuketeru~
The stars keep turning
kimi mo mita no?~
Do you see it too?
bisokudo no emooshon oikakete~
Chasing after a Time Lapse of emotion
kakugo no monogatari wo kasanete~
With a story of resolve overlaid
utagoe to tokimeki ga hibiki ai~
Singing voices and excitement ring together
afuredasu Time Lapse
The overflowing Time Lapse
mou osae kirenai~
I can't hold it any more
wo~ wo~ wo~wo~
hi ga ochite utagoe wa hoshi to nari~
The sun goes down, and the voice becomes a star
nagaredasu Time Lapse
Flowing like a Time Lapse
sou kanjitsuzukeru~
Yes, I still feel it