juudai na monda' kakaete nemuru
I sleep, with big problems
weighing down on me
aisareta hou ga tashika ni musou tek' da keredo
Though you can't beat that feeling
of being loved, it's true
tsumetai yume kara mezamete shibireru karada
When I awaken from cold dreams,
my body feels numb
kimi ga mabushii kara watashi wa kage ni nareru
You shine so brightly,
it could make me a shadow
iza fumikome
It's time to take that step
tashika na koto nado hitotsu mo nai keredo
Though there's nothing certain about it
osanai kokoro wo asu ni hakobu no sa
It carries my childish heart into tomorrow
aa karakara sawagu shikou tobash'te
It's time to blast out the thoughts
rattling around in my brain
aegari sh'teru kono inochi wo tsukai kiranakucha
And live, to its fullest, a life
I've been taking advances on for so long
ima kono toki mo daradara sugiru hi mo aish'te
But I also love the days I spend
lying around, doing nothing
kitto kimi ni ai ni yuku
So I know I'm going to go see you
itsuka kiete shimau mae ni
Before it all disappears some day