“Ame no nioi ni natsukashiku naru no wa nande na n’deshou ka.
“Why does the scent of the rain make me feel nostalgic?
Natsu ga chikadzuku to mune ga zawameku no wa nande na n’deshou ka.
Why does my heart clamor as summer approaches?
Hito ni warawaretara namida ga deru no wa nande na n’deshou ka.
Why do I cry when people laugh at me?
Soredemo itsuka mukuwareru kara to omoeba ii n’deshou ka.”
Is it all right to think that even so I’ll be rewarded someday?”
sayonara tte kotoba de konna ni mune o saite
With the word “goodbye” tearing so much at my chest,
ima mo tatta suushun no yuuyake ni ashi ga tomatte ita
I was standing still for just a few moments at sunset
“Sensei, jinsei soudan desu.
“Teacher, I want to talk about my life.
Kono saki dou nara raku desu ka.
What should I do from now on?
Sonna no daremo wakari wa shinai yo nante iwaremasu ka.
Are you just going to tell me ‘no one knows that’ or something?
Hora, kurushisa nante hoshii wake nai.
Look, it’s not that I want to suffer.
Nani mo shinaide ikite itai.
I just want to live without doing anything.
Aozora dake ga mitai no wa wagamama desu ka.”
Is it selfish to just want to look at the blue sky?”
“Mune ga itande mo uso ga tsukeru no wa nande na n’deshou ka.
“Why do I lie even though it makes my heart ache?
Warui hito bakari ga toku o shite’ru no wa nande na n’deshou ka.
Why do only bad people prosper?
Shiawase no moji ga okane o fukumu no wa nande na n’deshou ka.
Why is it that the character for ‘happiness’ includes the ￥ sign?
Hitotsu sen o nukeba tsurasa ni naru no wa waza to na n’deshou ka.
Is it on purpose that leaving out a single stroke turns it into the character for ‘pain’?”
seishun tte nefuda ga senaka ni hararete ite
With a price sticker saying “youth” stuck to my back
HICCHIKOKKU mitai na SASUPENSU o dokoka kitai shite ita
I was hoping in some way for Hitchcock-like suspense
“Sensei, dou demo ii n’desu yo.
“Teacher, I don’t care.
Ikite’ru dake de itai n’desu yo.
Just going on living causes me pain.
NIICHE mo FUROITO mo kono ana no umekata wa kakanai n’da.
Neither Nietzche nor Freud wrote about how to fill this hole.
Tada natsu no nioi ni me o tsumutte,
I just want to close my eyes in the scent of summer,
kumo no takasa o yubi de kakou.
And sketch out the height of the clouds with my fingers.
Omoide dake ga mitai no wa wagamama desu ka.”
Is it selfish to just want to relive memories?”
“DORAMACHIKKU ni hito ga shinu SUTORII tte ureru ja nai desu ka.
“A story where people die dramatically will sell, won’t it?
Hana no chirigiwa ni sura ne ga tsuku no mo iya ni narimashita.
I’ve come to hate that even the moment that a flower’s petals fall has a price on it.
Sensei no yume wa nan datta n’desu ka.
What was your dream, Teacher?
Otona ni naru to wasurechau mono nan desu ka.”
Did you forget it when you became an adult?”
“Sensei, jinsei soudan desu.
“Teacher, I want to talk about my life.
Kono saki dou nara raku desu ka.
What should I do from now on?
Namida ga hito o tsuyoku suru nante zenbu kiben deshita.
‘Tears make people stronger’ was nothing but sophism.
Aa, kono saki dou demo ii wake nakute, genjitsu dake ga chiratsuite,
Yes, it’s not that I don’t care what happens to me, it’s just that reality is flickering,
natsu ga tookute.
And summer is far away.
Kore demo hontou ni ii n’desu ka.
Is this really all right?
Kono mama ikite mo ii n’desu ka.
Can I go on living like this?
Sonna no kimi ni shika wakaranai yo nante iwaremasu ka.
Are you just going to tell me ‘only you can answer that’ or something?
tada natsu no nioi ni me o tsumuritai.
I just want to close my eyes in the scent of summer.
Itsumademo kaze ni fukaretai.
I want to feel the wind always.
Aozora dake ga mitai no wa wagamama desu ka.”
Is it selfish to just want to look at the blue sky?”
anata dake o shiritai no wa wagamama desu ka
Is it selfish if I just want to know you?