Kono Machi de Ima Kimi to
(Together with You, Right Here in These Streets)
Liella!
Composed by: Menma
Arranged by: Iehara Masaki
Written by: Miyajima Junko
itsumo machiawase yori juugo fun mae shuugou
We’re meeting up fifteen minutes earlier than usual today
eki no kaisatsu nukeru zawameki ni wakuwaku da ne~
I skip past the station gates, excitement bubbling in my heart
doko e mukau ka nante ki ni shinaide aruiteku
Let’s not think too much about where we’re going
issho ni sugosu tte koto sore ga ichiban daiji da yo~
What’s important is that you’re here with me
mirai no iro wa mada~ boyakete mieyashina~i
What does our future look like? I can’t really tell yet
tada hitotsu wakaru no wa~ kimi ga kimi ga suki da
But if there’s one thing I know for sure, is that I really, really like you
donna toki mo odoru you ni kousaten koete ike~
I’ll cross every intersection with a spring in my step no matter what happens
oshiyoseru hito no nami sururi surinuke jiyuu jizai sa~
Weaving through the gaps in the crowd, is this what it means to be free?
kimi wa sukoshi mae no hou de itazura ni waratteru~
Slightly ahead of me, you turn back with a mischievous smile on your face
arikitari na ima demo saikou no “ima” sa
Even an ordinary today feels extraordinary when I’m with you
kono yuujou wa kawaranai yo~
This friendship of ours is forever!
kotae no nai koto bakka ruupu shite zutto shabetteru
With only unanswerable questions on our lips, we go around in circles
petto botoru no shizuku yubi de moteasobi nagara~
Fingers tracing against the grooves of a water bottle sweating in the sun
tanoshii jikan te sa~ nazeka atto iu ma da ne~
Doesn’t time always seem to fly by when we’re having fun?
kokoro wa karappo de~ hazumu hazumu hikaru
With our hearts free of worries, we sparkle with excitement
yurume no rizumu odoru you ni ichibyou zutsu o asobe~
Enjoying each and every second, as if we were dancing to a slow rhythm
itsuka te o nobashite mo todokanaku naru hi ga kuru no kana
Will there come a day when I reach out, only to find that you’re gone?
soredemo iinda! akane iro ni somaru sora megakete~
But that doesn’t matter for now! With my eyes set on the sky, dyed a deep red
ookina koe de kimi ni yakusoku suru yo
I make a promise to you at the top of my lungs
kono shunkan wa eien datte!~
That this moment will last forever!
Picture time, everyone!
Let’s go!
Ready, and!
sekai wa dokomade~ tsuzuite yukun daro~
Just how far does the world go on for?
wakaranai kara kimi to~ ima dake o~ miteru yo~
I have no idea, so I’ll focus on here and now, where you’re with me
donna toki mo odoru you ni kousaten koete ike~
I’ll cross every intersection with a spring in my step no matter what happens
oshiyoseru hito no nami oyoide yukou kono machi de ima~
Swimming against the wave of people, right here in these streets
kimi wa sukoshi mae no hou de itazura ni waratteru~
Slightly ahead of me, you turn back with a mischievous smile on your face
arikitari na koto demo zenbu tokubetsu sa
Even an ordinary today feels extraordinary when I’m with you
watashitachi zutto tomodachi da yo~
We’ll be friends forever!