haiiro ni shiranda kotoba wa KAPUCHIINO mitai na iro shite’ru
My words that had faded to grey are now a color like cappuccino
iiwake wa ii yo madobe ni oite kite
Enough of the excuses, leave them by the window
kazoekirenai yo
There are too many to count
haiiro ni shiranda kokoro wa KAPUCHIINO mitai na iro shite’ru
My heart that had faded to grey is now a color like cappuccino
iiwake wa ii yo aorou KAPUCHIINO
Enough of the excuses, I’ll gulp down cappuccino
odoketa furi shite
And pretend to be an idiot
saa tayutau you ni ame nagare
The rain flows as if indecisive
bokura ni arasu hana ni obore
We drown in the flowers storming around us
kimi ga asenai you na omoide o
So you won’t fade away, I keep this memory–
douka, douka, douka kimi ga afurenai you ni
I hope, I hope, I hope you don’t overflow
nami matsu kaigan kurenai yuu sasu hi
The beach awaits the waves; a red evening sun shines
mado ni hansha shite
They’re reflected in the window
hachigatsu no VISUBII shiosai machibouke
Visby in August, the roar of the sea
umikaze hitotsu de
I wait in vain for a single sea breeze
natsu oyoida hana no shirosa, yoi no ame
The white of the flowers that swam in the summer, the evening rain
nagaru yoru ni obore
Drown in the flowing night
daremo asenai you na hana hitotsu
So no one will fade away, keep this flower–
douka, douka, douka mune no uchigawa ni sashite
I hope, I hope, I hope you’ll stick it to the inside of your heart
zutto okashii n’da
Things have been strange for a long time
ikikata hitotsu oshiete hoshii dake
I just want someone to tell me one way to live
haraeru mono nante boku ni wa mou nai kedo
I have no way to pay for it anymore
nani mo kotaerarenai nara kotoba hitotsu demo ii yo
But if it’s too hard to answer, a single word would be enough
wakaranai yo
I don’t understand
hontou ni wakannai n’da yo
I seriously don’t get it at all
saa tayutau you ni ame nagare
The rain flows as if indecisive
bokura ni arasu hana ni obore
We drown in the flowers storming around us
kimi ga asenai you ni kaku uta o
So you won’t fade away, I write this song–
douka, douka, douka ima mo wasurenai you ni
I hope, I hope, I hope you haven’t forgotten it even now
(douka)
(I hope)
mata hitotsu natsu ga owatte, hana hitotsu o mune ni daite,
Another summer comes to an end, and I hold a single flower in my heart,
nagaru mabuta no ura de
Flowing beneath my eyelids
kimi ga asenai you ni kono uta o
So you won’t fade away, I wrote this song
douka, douka, kimi ga afurenai you ni
I hope, I hope you don’t overflow
(douka)
(I hope)