kawaranai fuukei asai shougo
The scenery doesn’t change; on a faded afternoon
kouka shita, ai nijou, nekorobu mama
I’m lying in the deep indigo beneath the overpass
hakushi no jinsei ni hakushu no ne ga hitotsu natte iru
I hear a single clap for my blank-page life
karappo na jibun o kyou mo utatte ita
I was singing about my own emptiness today, as usual
(wow wow wow)
kawaranai you ni
So things wouldn’t change,
kimi ga shuyaku no PUROTTO o kaku NOOTO no naka
I wrote a story starring you in my notebook
tomatta GASU suidou seken mo NYUUSU mo shosen taningoto
My gas and water being cut off, society, and the news are all someone else’s problem
kono jinsei sae hora, INKU mitai da
Look, my life is like ink
ano koro zutto atama ni egaita yume mo otona ni naru hodo jikou ni natte iku
The dream I had when I was young gets closer to its expiration date as I get older
tada, tada kumo o miagete mo
Though I just, I just look up at the clouds
shikai wa kyou mo nagareru mama
As usual, they flow through my field of vision
tooku aoida yoru ni hana oyogu
In the distant night sky I looked up at, flowers swam
haru to mimagau hodo ni
So many that it could be mistaken for spring
kimi o tada miushinau you ni
As if I’d just lost sight of you
korobanai you ni shita o muita
I looked down so I wouldn’t trip
jinsei wa dou ni mo dakyou de dekite’ru
Life is made of nothing but compromises
kokoro mo unmei mo RABU SONGU mo jinsei mo shinjinai
I don’t believe in hearts or fate or love songs or life
shosen urenai nara zenbu ga muda da
After all, if you can’t sell something it has no value
waza to koboshita yume de egaita ima ni nesobetta mama de jikou o matte iru
I intentionally discarded the present I dreamed of, and now I’m lying here waiting for its expiration date
tada, tada mabuta no uragawa
Behind my eyelids, I just, I just saw
tooku egaku kimi o mita mama
An imagined, distant vision of you
NOOTO, usui yasumi ni hana oyogu
In my notebook, flowers swim in the corner of a faded night
boku no me ni mata hitotsu
One more is in my eye
jinsei wa dakyou no renzoku na n’da
Life is just one compromise after another
sonna koto tou ni wakatte’ta n’da
I learned that pretty fast
ERUMA, kimi na n’da yo
Elma, it’s you
kimi dake ga boku no ongaku na n’da
You alone are my music
kono uta wa ato hachijuuji
There are only eighty more characters in this song
jinsei no kachi wa, owarikata darou kara
Because maybe the only value of a life is in the way it ends
tada, tada kimi dake o egake
I just, I just picture you
shikai no ai mo nijinda mama
As even the indigo filling my vision is blurred
tooku aoida sora ni hana oyogu
In the distant sky I looked up at, flowers swam
kono me oou ai nijou
Deep indigo covers my eyes
tada, tada
It’s just, it’s just…
(hoho hoho)
tooku aoida sora, kimi ga suzumu
In the distant sky I looked up at, you are cooling off
tada yoru o oyogu you ni
As if you were just swimming in the night