hanare banare itsu no watashi
My once upon self, whom I parted ways with,
sashinoberareteiru te no naka
reaches her hand out to me,
kagi o kaketa chiisai hako ni
within which is a small locked box
shitteita hazu no michi no mikaku
with the taste of the path I thought I had known hidden inside.
itamu kizu o hoobaru goto ni mata
Every time my face is filled with aching pain,
netami ga netsuryou ga tsumetasa ga hikari ga kyozetsu ga kibou ga
all the jealousy, warmth, coldness, light, rejection, and hope
karamariai nani mo dekizu ni
become tangled up, making me unable to do a thing
sakebu
I scream
torokeru amakute kuroi kanjou wa shokoratoru
This sweet and black emotion that's melting away is Chocolatl
risou nante mou moetsukite shimatta no!
All of my ideals are burning away!
yowamushi no miminari wa yamanai
The noise of my weak self would not stop ringing in my ear.
afureteiku watashi o
Find my overflowing self.
mitsukete