Waracchau kurai mattaku chigau watashitachi
We two are so different that it's funny
Show window wo utsuru sugata sae
Even our reflections in the display window too
Taiyou mitai ni anata ga hohoemu to
When you smile, it's like the sun
Odayaka na kuuki ga nagareru
And I can feel a gentle wind begin to blow
Arikitari na nichijou de sae mo
Even these ordinary uneventful days
Anata to nara kagayakidasu
Start shining when I'm with you
Tatoe nani ga okita to shite mo
No matter what might happen
Tama ni kizutsuki kizutsukete mo
Even if we sometimes hurt each other
Nanigenai hi wo shinjiteite
I'll keep believing in these unremarkable days