yasashii koto wa~ wasurenaideiru~
I won’t forget the kindness.
itsudatte sayonara no ato ni wa~
It’s always there, even after goodbyes.
niteiru mono wo~ omoidashite miru~
I try to remember things that feel familiar,
shiranai koto bakari kazoete sa~
Counting all the things I don’t yet know.
sunao na mama de kimi ni hanasetara
If I could speak to you just as I am, without holding back,
atataka na merodi dake ga kitto
Only a warm melody would fall upon this town.
kono machi ni furu darou~
yoru no futari asa no nioi
The two of us at night, the scent of morning,
boyaketa shiryoku de saguri atteiru
Groping for each other with blurred vision,
todokisou ni naru no wa iki wo tomete shimau kara
We nearly reach each other, but then hold our breath.
yoake no doa~ tataite~
I’ve walked this path, knocking on the door of dawn,
kou naranai you ni aruite kita no da~
Hoping not to end up like this.
wakeatta kakera ookii hou wo ageyou~
The fragments we shared—I'll give you the larger piece.
amai kuriimu chanto suki~ da yo~
And yes, I really do like the sweet cream.
yoru ni sotto~ hari wo otoshite~
Gently, I lower the needle onto the record in the night,
sabishii nyuusu ga yatte kuru made~
Waiting for you until the lonely news arrives.
kimi wo matteita no sa~
Yes, I was waiting for you. Yes, I was waiting for you.
kimi wo matteita no sa aa~
yoru no futari~ asa no nioi
The two of us at night, the scent of morning,
kirei na~ te to te de saguri atteiru
Reaching out with beautiful hands, feeling our way through,
umaku ienai~ no wa~ iki wo tomete shimau kara~
Unable to speak well, because we’re holding our breath,
asa ga konai~ kono machi no subete~
As if morning might never come to this town.
yoake no doa wo tataite~
I’ve walked this path, knocking on the door of dawn, hoping not to end up like this.
kou naranai you ni aruite kita no da~
tatoeba futari~ ochite kita tenshi~
Imagine, for example, that the two of us were fallen angels,
doko kara yatte kita kamo wasurete~ sa
Forgetting even where we came from.