mita koto nai yume no kidou oikakete
Let's chase the orbit of unseen dreams!
Shining Road
hashiridasu kono kimochi
My feelings run
massugu ni ikioi yoku kimi o sagashiteta yo
as I'm vigorously looking for you,
chotto matte nante muri tobidasou
Wait a minute! This can't be,
bokutachi no naka no yuuki ga sawaideru
It's the courage that touches us inside
itsumo no sekai ga atarashii tobira o
The world's always full of
(motto)
kakushiteru no
(more)
hidden new doors
(Let's go!)
zenbu aketai yo hora issho ni ne!
I want to open them, let's look for them together!
hajimetai! My Story
I want to start my story
(saa ima da)
(Right now),
aoi sora ga matteru
the blue sky is waiting for us,
yume o dakishimete Jumping Heart
It's a jumping heart that embraces our dreams,
sore dake de ashita e to susumeru seishun masshigura!?
a youth that advances straight to tomorrow,
hajimatta toki no
It's our time to start our
(Sunshine Story)
(sunshine story),
tokimeki zutto daiji ni ne
the excitement's important to me,
yume o tsukamae ni yuku yo
Let’s go and take hold of our dreams
donna koto ga okoru no ka wakaranai no mo tanoshimi sa
No matter what happens, even if we don't understand, let's look forward to it
Open Mind
tsutaenakya tsutawaranai
We have to say it but we can't
saisho kara kanpeki ni dekiru hazu wa nai kara
Since no one should be able to do it perfectly from the start
toriaezu genki ni tobidasou
For now, let’s fly energetically
bokutachi no start line goal wa tooi kana
From our start line, I wonder if the goal is far away.
mabushii sekai de yobu koe ga kikoeta
In this shining world, I heard you call out for me
(motto)
kiite mitakute
(More)
I wanted to hear you
(Let's go!)
hikari no mukou e hora issho ni ne!
(Let’s go!)
Towards the other side of the light
kaetai na! My Future
I want to change my future
(saa doko e)
(So, where to)
taiyou ga noboru you ni
by rising up like the sun
yume yo kagayaite Charging Heart
Our dreams shined Charging heart
chikara ippai kanaeyou negai o seishun pikkari da!?
Let’s use all our strength to grant our desires Isn’t youth surprising!?
kaetai to omou
“I want to change”, I thought
(Sunshine Mission)
(Sunshine mission)
kimochi ga kitto daiji da yo
Our feelings are surely important
yume o tsukamae ni yuku yo
Let’s go and take hold of our dreams
minna to nara setsumei wa dekinai kedo daijoubu sa
If it’s with everyone, it’s fine even if I can’t explain it
Jumping Heart datte hajimetai koto ga
Jumping heart But the fact that I want to start
Charging Heart ima mitsukatta bakkari
Charging heart I found it just about now
Goal wa doko? doko darou? wakaranai!
Where is the goal? I wonder where it is? I don’t know
wakaranai demo ne tanoshi sou da yo
I don’t know, but let’s still have fun
hajimetai! My Story aoi sora ga matteru
I want to start my story; The blue sky is waiting for us,
yume o dakishimete Jumping Heart
It's a jumping heart that embraces our dreams,
sore dake de ashita e to susumeru seishun masshigura!?
a youth that advances straight to tomorrow,
hajimatta toki no
It's our time to start our
(Sunshine Story)
(sunshine story),
tokimeki zutto daiji ni ne
the excitement's important to me,
yume o tsukamae ni yuku yo
so let's go and catch our dreams!
donna koto ga okoru no ka wakaranai mirai
Let's look forward happily and see what happens!
yume o tsukamae ni yuku yo
Let’s go and take hold of our dreams
minna to nara setsumei wa dekinai kedo daijoubu sa… masshigura!
If it’s with everyone, it’s fine even if I can’t explain it… so let’s go straight ahead!