kiite kudasai
For your listening pleasure…
Beautiful Birthday
"Beautiful Birthday"
I'm glad I met you
(I'm glad I met you)
hieta yume ni tsukisasatta
Piercing into the chilled dream,
aa hikari
(aa)
Ah-ah- (Ah-ah-) Was a ray of light
I need you right now
(I need you right now)
mabushii mama boku no subete
In all your brightness, you embraced
aa dakishimeta
(aa)
Ah-ah (Ah-ah) All of me
(ohoh oh oh oh ohoh oh oh ohoh)
jigoku datte kamawanai
It doesn't matter even if it's hell
anata no moto de ikireru nara
If I can be where you are
sono tabi kanjita no wa
That was what I felt at that time
kamisama nante
Even God was unnecessary, in such a
iranai kurai no
kanpekina
Perfect (Beautiful World)
(beautiful world)
sekai wa anata wo matteta
The world has (Don't let go) been waiting for you
(Don't let go)
chiisaku mo ookiku
Your small yet big shining figure
kagayaku sugata wa
kako sura someagete
Can dye even the past
mou soko ni kage wanai
(Don't let go)
By now (Don't let go) The shadows there are gone
sakebu
I'll shout it out, my gratitude and Bless your Birthday
kansha to
Bless your Birthday