Zenbu tenki no sei de ii yo
We can blame it all on the weather
Kono kimazu sa mo kentaikan mo
All this awkwardness and exhaustion
Taiyou wa kakurenagara shiranpuri
The sun hides away, pretending not to see
Gatagoto yureru manin densha
A packed train clatters along the track
Surechigau no wa junkyuu ressha
It brushes past a local express
Rinkaku no nai kumo no hyoujou wo sagashitemiru
I'm gonna search for feelings
in a shapeless cloud
"Sakusha no kimochi wo kotaenasai"
The test asks, "How was
the author feeling here?"
Ittai nani ga seikai nan dai?
What could the right answer possibly be?
Yotei chouwa no scenario fuminuite
Breaking through the script
of pre-established harmony
Aoi haru nante mon wa
Everyone talks about the
"springtime of life"
Boku ni wa niawanai nda
And I'm just not cut out for that
Soredemo shitteru kara ichido shikanai shunkan wa
Yet I know that this moment,
which will never come again,
Hakana sa wo hara nderu
is rich with evanescence
Zettai wasurete yaranai yo
I will never forget, ever
Itsuka shinu made nan kai datte
So many times before I die someday...
Konna koto mo attatte waratteyan no sa
I'll laugh thinking about what it was like
Semai kyoushitsu shinkuu joutai
A cramped classroom, existing in a vacuum
Shounen tachi wa seishun zenkai
The boys are enjoying their youth
Kiritorisen de kugireta boku no sekai
My world is separated by a perforated line
Kirai na boku no rettoukan to
This hateful feeling of inferiority
Tanin to chigau yuuetsukan to
Is my sense of superiorty over everyone else
Semegiau zetsumyou na kanjou
A sublime emotion that's in constant conflict
Ittai nani yatten da
What on Earth am I doing?
"Wakaru wakaru, onaji kimochi sa"
"I totally get it! I feel the same way."
Honto ni sou omotteimasu ka?
Do you actually think that?
Tajirogu boku no ki mo shiranaide
You don’t even know how much that irks me
Dareka ga hajimeru kyou wa
Someone else's beginning to today
Boku ni wa owari no kyou sa
Is nothing but an ending to me
Kurikaesu ashibumi ni mirai kara no yobigoe ga
As I repeat my footsteps, the future is calling to me
Hibiiteru "susume yo" to
"Keep moving forward," it echoes
Unmei ya kiseki nante mono wa
But things like fate and miracles
Kitto boku ni wa mottai nai ya
Are surely wasted on me
Nanto naku no ippo wo fumidasu dake sa
I can only take the steps as they come
Otona hodo kusattemo inakute
I'm not as spoiled as an adult
Kodomo hodo tensai janai ga
But I'm no child genius either
Boku wa ima jinsei no chuukan da
I'm right in the middle of my life
Kaze nioite kare sou de
I feel like the wind's leaving me behind
Hisshi ni kurai tsuiteru
So I'm desperately clinging on
Itsumo no kane no ne mo madogiwa ni tsunda hokori mo
That familiar sound of the bell
That dust piled up on the window sill
Kyoushitsu no nioi datte
Even the smell of the classroom
Zettai wasurete yaranai yo
I will never forget, ever
Itsuka shinu made nan kai datte
So many times before I die someday...
Konna koto mo attatte waratteyan no sa
I'll laugh thinking about what it was like