The culture festival is behind us.
We'd better start thinking
about our next concert, right?
That's right!
Write us lots of new songs, Ryo!
Just waiting for inspiration to strike.
Let me know if there's anything I can do!
Anything?
Kita-chan! Don't say that to Ryo
unless you're ready to follow through!
You can start by treating me to gyudon.
Dekireba sekai wo boku wa nurikaetai
If I could, I'd repaint the world
Sis! Hurry up or you'll be late!
Sensou wo nakusu you na daisoreta koto janai
Nothing as drastic like getting rid of wars
A-Awesome...
Dakedo chotto sore mo aru yo na
But maybe, there's a bit of that too
I'm s-sorry! I haven't f-forgotten you!
Forgive me!
Haiyuu ya eiga star ni wa narenai
Can't be an actor or a movie star
She's at it again.
Sore dokoro ka kimi no mae de sae mo jouzu ni waraenai
I can't even laugh naturally in front of you for that matter
Be back later.
Sonna boku ni sube wa nai yo na
What's there for a guy like me to do?
Aa...
Nani wo machigatta?
What did I do wrong
Sore sae mo wakaranain da
Can't even figure that out
Rolling rolling
Rolling, rolling,
Hajime kara mottenai no ni mune ga itanda
My heart lamenting over what was never mine
Bokura wa kitto kono saki mo
We'll probably continue to
Kokoro karamatte rolling rolling
Our hearts entangled, rolling, rolling,
Itetsuku jimen wo korogaru you ni hashiridashita
Start to run across the frozen ground as if we're rolling
Akai, akai chiisana kuruma wa kimi wo nosete
The small red car takes her away
Tooku mukou no kado wo magatte
Makes a turn at the far off corner
Koko kara wa mienaku natta
Disappearing from my vision
(Koko kara wa mienaku natta)
Nani wo nakushita?
What was it I lost?
Sore sae mo wakaranain da
Can't even figure that out
Rolling rolling
Rolling, rolling,
Hajime kara mottenai no ni mune ga itanda
My heart lamenting over what that was never mine
Bokura wa kitto kono saki mo
We'll probably continue to
Kokoro karamatte rolling rolling
Our hearts entangled, rolling, rolling,
Itetsuku sekai wo korogaru you ni hashiridashita
Start to run across the frozen ground as if we're rolling
Wow
Ooh yeah