Motto yumemite
Let's dream some more and keep moving forward
Minna susumou yo
Ippai yumemite
Let's dream a lot and keep moving forward
Minna susumou yo
Doko made mo
I'll stretch my hand out however far
Te wo nobasou
Tokimeki wa itsumo
The thrills inside me
Bokura no mune no naka de
Have always been radiantly glowing
Kagayaitetanda ne
(Tooku e)
I feel like I can go however far when you're smiling with me
Ikesou da yo tte sa
Warau kimi to
Zutto issho ni yume wo miyou
(Zutto)
Let's keep dreaming forever and ever
Owaranai yume miyou yo
Let's dream a dream that won't end
(Ah singing dreaming)
Massugu kakenuketara
As we dash straight forward
Genkai nante itsu no ma ni ka koechau yo
We find that at some point we've gone past out limits
Akiramenai kokoro ga ashita wo
(Oikaketai)
This heard of mine that won't give up
(Wants to keep chasing)
Will go and alter tomorrow
Kaete yukun da
(Singing now)
Kimi to kakenuketeku taisetsu na hibi
The days I dashed through with you are so precious
Sora no ao sa mabushii ne
The sky is a dazzling blue
Shinjiteru yo nanda tte dekiru to
(Shinjiteru yo)
I believe that we can do anything
(I really do)
Suki no chikara wa tsuyoin da yo saikyou sa~
The power of love is the strongest thing there is
SINGING, DREAMING, NOW!