Zenbu tenki no sei de ii yo
We can blame it all on the weather
Kono kimazu sa mo kentaikan mo
All this awkwardness and exhaustion
Taiyou wa kakurenagara shiranpuri
The sun hides away, pretending not to see
Gatagoto yureru manin densha
A packed train clatters along the track
Surechigau no wa junkyuu ressha
It brushes past a local express
Rinkaku no nai kumo no hyoujou wo sagashitemiru
I'm gonna search for feelings
in a shapeless cloud
"Sakusha no kimochi wo kotaenasai"
The test asks, "How was
the author feeling here?"
Ittai nani ga seikai nan dai?
What could the right answer possibly be?
Yotei chouwa no scenario fuminuite
Breaking through the script
of pre-established harmony
Aoi haru nante mon wa
Everyone talks about the
"springtime of life"
Boku ni wa niawanai nda
And I'm just not cut out for that
Soredemo shitteru kara ichido shikanai shunkan wa
Yet I know that this moment,
which will never come again,
Hakana sa wo hara nderu
is rich with evanescence
Zettai wasurete yaranai yo
I will never forget, ever
Itsuka shinu made nan kai datte
So many times before I die someday...
Konna koto mo attatte waratteyan no sa
I'll laugh thinking about what it was like
Kaze nioite kare sou de
I feel like the wind's leaving me behind
Hisshi ni kurai tsuiteru
So I'm desperately clinging on
Itsumo no kane no ne mo madogiwa ni tsunda hokori mo
That familiar sound of the bell
That dust piled up on the window sill
Kyoushitsu no nioi datte
Even the smell of the classroom
Zettai wasurete yaranai yo
I will never forget, ever
Itsuka shinu made nan kai datte
So many times before I die someday...
Konna koto mo attatte waratteyan no sa
I'll laugh thinking about what it was like