Hey DJ kamase yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ
Do it, yeah yeah yeah, that superb-feeling
Kibun joujou↑↑ no
Hari otose oto narase party night
Needle, drop it, blast the sound, party night
Nomou 'right 'right 'right
Let's drink, alright alright alright, let's all dance!
Minna de odore!
Hip-Pop
(People)
Hip-pop people, play that miracle number
Kakete yo miracle number
Yo!
Konna jidai ni wakachiau music
Yo! Music that we share in an era like this
Sagashitakute mawasu chikyuugi
We want to search for it, a globe that spins
Guratsuku fuantei seikatsu
Wavering, unstable lives
Sore dakara balance juushi
That's why we emphasize balance
Yoi koto bakari janai kara "ganbareru!"
Not everything is great, so I can try my best!
Saiaku na hi ni kick
Kick the worst of days
Saikidou no button click!
Click the restart button!
DJ kakete!! ima trip
DJ, play it! Now, trip
Shareteru beat ni notte~
Let's groove to the hip beat and shake our feeling bodies
Kanjiru karada yurasou yo
Hey DJ shashare yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, butt in, yeah yeah yeah, that superb-feeling
Kibun joujou↑↑ no
Nami ni notte hajiketobe funky night
Wave, ride it and fly off, funky night
Nomou 'right 'right 'right
Let's drink, alright alright alright, let's all dance!
Minna de odore!
Hip-Pop
(People)
Hip-pop people, a miracle number until the morn
Asa made miracle number
Hey DJ kamase yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, do it, yeah yeah yeah
Nomou 'right 'right 'right
Let's drink, alright alright alright
Hey DJ kamase yeah yeah yeah
Hey DJ, do it, yeah yeah yeah