aiiro ni toku nibiiro no saitekikai
Dissolve to indigo blue, the best answer to dark gray
shikou kairo idomu toiki no shoumei
Thought patterns challenge proof of breath
junpaku ni tou shikkoku no shinjitsu ni~
Question the pure white on the pitch-black truth
zengo fukaku kuramu joushiki to Answer
Lose consciousness, common sense and answers fade
aiiro ni toku nibiiro no fujunbutsu ni
Preach to indigo blue, the dark gray impurity
kido airaku yureru toiki no shoumei
Various moods, wavering proof of breath
junshin ni tou gokusai no shinsou ni~
Question innocence on the multicolored facts
unsan mushou tokeru hiiro no Question
Vanish like smoke, the scarlet question is resolved
togisumase~ togisumase~
Sharpen your senses, sharpen your senses
nerau seorii minogasanu you
So you don’t miss the target theory
kakujitsu ni~ kakujitsu ni~
Be precise, be precise
shinjitsu dake wo ima rokuon
Only what’s true, record now
heiki tte sumashita~ sono kamen wo kowashita nara~
Once you break your mask of acting tough
meneki mo shinda~ uso darake no sekai nuritsubuse~
Paint out the world of lost immunity, a world full of lies
ittsuu mo dare ni mo~ todokanai to shitatte~
Even if one message doesn’t reach anyone
uchinuku shinjitsu wa itsumo~ tadashisa dake~
It’s always only what is right that shoots through the truth
tada, sono shoumei
It’s just proof of that
mimi sumase~ mimi sumase~
Listen closely, listen closely
nigoru seorii machigaenu you~
So you don’t mess up the muddy theory
fukakujitsu na~ fukakujitsu na~
Uncertain, uncertain
genjitsu dake wo ima Rec Out
Only uncertain reality, output now
heiki tte kowashita~ sono kamen wo hirotte~
Once you pick up your mask which you broke while acting tough
Fake it somatta~ uso darake no sekai wo tadashite~
Fake it, correct the stained world, a world full of lies
isshou dare ni mo~ wakaranai to shitatte~
Even if no one ever understands
ikinuku genjitsu wa itsumo~ seikai dake~
It’s always only what is right that survives reality
tada, sono shoumei
It’s just proof of that
aiiro ni toku nibiiro no saitekikai
Solving to indigo blue, the best answer to dark gray
shinjitsu ni tou kore ga watashi dake no Answer
Seek the truth, I’m the only one with my answer