(wah huh hah huuuh)
sassou to shoubu shite
Unhesitatingly, I demand a fight
yacchau kedo makechatte
I’ll do my best, yet still lose
fugainai nai ne
It’s rather disappointing
shoushin tenshin
So, let’s shift away from that grief
kibun wa sunsunde mo
Even if I’m feeling sorry
shippo de henji shiyou
I’ll still reply with my tail
chounai de wai wai shite
This town is noisy
inu made bauwau de
The dogs go bow-wow
tende meimei de
All the time
shunkashuutou
No matter the season
shippai shitatte warai tobasou
So, let’s just laugh off our failures
ano koro to onaji you ni kokoro tsumuide
Connecting our hearts together like that one time
kono machi de deaeta kiseki
Meeting in this town was a miracle
(huh hah huuuh)
kanaete yo
Please grant it
zenkai da wa taiya shou ippai
Carry those tires and go full throttle
warning mada kiki kanri enjoi
Warning: There are still crises to manage, so enjoy life
toridori saita iro kyanbasu kakenuke
As various colours run off the canvas
sunset da wa kangaete bakari ja
It’s sunset, so don’t think about things
sou mae he!
And move ahead!
hora donna iro datte yume kasanete
See, it doesn’t matter what colour our dreams may be
motto asobou ne
So, let’s just keep on playing
(huh hah)