a~
koi wo shita no wa
I fell in love with you
nee mae muite
Hey, look forward
atashi wa koko ni iru desho?
I’m here, aren’t I?
dakara mou nakanaide
So don’t cry anymore
kokoro ga wareta toki mo tokubetsu na hibi wo kureta
You made every day special for me, even when my heart was broken
sasai ni kakechigaeta aka-iro
The color red, on just a little bit wrong
ano hi no rouka no shiro-iro
The white color of the hallway that day
hajimete mo saigo mo
The beginning, the end,
ima mo mau hanabira ni kizami okuru yo
And this moment, I'll engrave the dancing flower petals and gift it to you
darling
Darling
ochiru ame ni utsuru
In the falling rain,
futari sekai wa daremo shiranai
No one knows about the world of us two
a~
koi wo shita no wa
I fell in love with you
itsu kara ka naita no wa nandome ka
I wonder how many times I cried for you since
kazoeru to yoru ga akeru wa
When I tried to count, dawn already broke the night
komaru na…
So troublesome...
darling
Darling
tsutaetakatta koto wa
What I wanted to tell you
ima mo
Is the same now
mukashi mo zutto
As it was then
onaji mama da yo
And always has been,
darling
Darling
mayowanu you aruite ikeru
It’s a single guidepost
tatta hitotsu no michishirube
So we won’t lose our way