iroaseta shashin, MEMORY
Faded photos, memories
shiawase na jikan, kiseki
Happy times, a trajectory
omoide no naka no watashi~
Me in my recollections
kedo sude ni tanin mitai
But I already feel like a stranger
ano toki no jibun janai
I'm not who I was back then
iroai, negai, I~DENTITY~
Hues, wishes, and identity
kawatte (shimatta to~)
Someone (will say)
dareka ga~ (iu darou~)
I've (changed)
mae e to susumu tabi~
Every time I make progress
(dakedo~) mou, enryo nante iranai
(But) I don't need to hold back again
dare no teigi demo nai
I will not follow anyone else's definition
watashi de are~
Be myself
genkai nante hontou wa soko ni nai
There are actually no limits there
kutsugaese, nurikaete
Overturn it by making history
kenzai seyo kako o koeteku hikari
Actualize yourself, the light that will transcend the past
kono sora o someru hodo tsuyoku
Bright enough to shines this sky
(WOW OH OH OHOHOH OH OH OHOH~)
dare yori mo
More than anyone else
nani yori mo
(WOW OH OH OHOHOH OH OH OHOH~)
More than anything
kinou no watashi o uchiyabutte
Break down who I was yesterday
arifureta CYAN, KEY PLATE
Ordinary cyan, a key plate
MAGENTA, YELLOW
Magenta, and yellow
yakimashi sareta you na hibi
Days like reprints
soko ni kagayaki nante nai
There is no brilliance there
soko ni imi ya kachi wa nai
There is no meaning or value there
teikaizoudo na nisemono da~
What low-resolution shams
juunin~ (toiro no)
Other people paint the world (in their own ways)
dareka no~ (fude ato)
And their brushstrokes overlap (everywhere)
mazariau sekai no~ (naka de~)
In such a (world)
saa, dare yori mo senretsu ni
Now is the time to strike it with your whole existence
CANVAS o saku you ni
More vividly than anyone else
takakitsukero~
As if you tear the canvas
mirai nante jitsu wa doko ni mo nai
There is actually no future anywhere
egakidase, jibun no te de
Create one with your own hands
genzai dake ga sonzai no shoumei
The present is the only proof of your existence
kizamikome kinou yori tsuyoku
Leave a stronger mark than yesterday
sono ao wa sora yori mo sunde iru ka~?
Is that blue clearer than the sky?
sono aka wa yuuyake o yakikireru ka~?
Can that red burn off the sunset glow?
tsuki yori mo, hoshi yori mo, yoru o ugate
More than the moon, more than the stars, pierce the night
DYE THE SKY IN MY HUE
WOW OHOHOH YEAH YEAH~
genkai nante hontou wa soko ni nai
There are actually no limits there
kutsugaese, jibun sae
Redefine all, even yourself
kenzai seyo kako o koeteku hikari
Actualize yourself, the light that will transcend the past
kono sora o someru hodo tsuyoku
Bright enough to shines this sky
(WOW OH OH OHOHOH OH OH OHOH~)
dare yori mo
More than anyone else
nani yori mo
(WOW OH OH OHOHOH OH OH OHOH~)
More than anything
sekai no subete o uchiyabutte
Smash everything in the world