Takaramono o mitsuketa kodomo no you ni
Like a child who has found a treasure
Kanade hajimetanda yume o
I started to play my dreams
Kirari kibou hibikaseru no
I'll make my glittering hopes resound
Dokomademo hirogare watashi no Symphony~
So that it can be heard everywhere, my symphony
Zutto taisetsu ni shimatteta
I had always treasured
Ichiban daisuki na koto
What is most precious to me
Doushitara kanaerareru no?
But when I wondered how to make it come true,
Wakaranakute tachidomatte ita
I stopped because I didn't know
Chansu wa aru hi totsuzen
One day an opportunity
Me no mae ni maiorite kita
Suddenly landed in front of me
Omou katachi to chigatte mo
Although it was different from what I imagined,
Sotto ryoute o nobashitanda
I slowly raised my arms towards it
Gikochi naku kizamu ippo ga
One clumsy step forward
Patto azayaka ni sekai o kaeteku
Can change the world in a flash
Nani ga matsu no? Nani o yareru no?
What's waiting for me? What can I do?
Yuuki dashite susumou~
Gather courage and move forward
Chippoke na kinou made no watashi janai
I'm no longer the insignificant me of yesterday
Kanade hajimetanda yume o
Since I've started to play my dreams
Maku ga agaru koko kara saki wa
The curtain rises, what awaits beyond
Mune ni egaiteta suteeji
Is the stage that I drew in my heart
Dekikkonai yotte omotteta koto mo
If I take a step towards it,
Fumidaseba hora kanaunda
Even what I thought was impossible will come true
Kirari kibou hibikaseru no
I'll make my glittering hopes resound
Dokomademo hirogare watashi no Symphony~
So that it can be heard everywhere, my symphony
Guzuguzu shiteta kako ni
If I could send a message
Messeeji o okureru no nara
To the hesitant me from the past
"Ima wa tanoshii yo" tte iitai!
I would tell her "I'm having fun now!"
Datte konna ni takanatteru yo
After all, my heart is beating this fast
Nandemo dekisou na anoko mo
That girl who seems able to do anything
Itsumo warai tayasanai anoko mo
That girl who never stops laughing
Mayoi nagara tomadoi nagara
Despite being worried, despite feeling lost
Kitto yume o miteru~
She never loses sight of her dreams
Totte oki no watashi rashii fureezu o
In order to someday find
Itsuka mitsukerareru you ni
The perfect phrase for myself
Hajimete demo chousen shite wa
Even if it's the first time, I'll take the challenge
Inoru no douka todoite!
Please let my prayer reach you!
Haruka tooku de nagareteru merodi
I listened carefully to the melody
Kobosazu mimi o sumashite
That is being played someplace faraway
Shiranai tobira akete yukou
Let's open the door to the unknown
Itsumademo owarasenai yo Symphony~
I won't ever let this symphony end
Migite no koyubi to hidarite no koyubi o musunde
I join together my right hand's little finger and my left hand's little finger
Jibun ni yakusoku shiyou
While I make myself a promise
Kyou no kimochi zutto wasurenai yo~
"I will never forget these feelings"
Chippoke na kinou made no watashi janai
I'm no longer the insignificant me of yesterday
Kanade hajimetanda yume o
Since I've started to play my dreams
Maku ga agaru koko kara saki wa
The curtain rises, what awaits beyond
Mune ni egaiteta suteeji
Is the stage that I drew in my heart
Dekikkonai yotte omotteta koto mo
If I take a step towards it,
Fumidaseba hora kanaunda
Even what I thought was impossible will come true
Kirari kibou hibikaseru no
I'll make my glittering hopes resound
Dokomademo hirogatteke
Let's make them spread everywhere
Rarara rarara rarara~ saa!
Rarara rarara rarara~
C'mon!
Atarashii watashi
Towards a new me
Ima, hajimaru yo Symphony~
The symphony is starting now