Nariyamanakute nani ga warui
What's wrong with not
letting my sound die down?
Seishun de nani ga warui
What's wrong with being young?
(Wow, wow, yeah!)
(Wow, wow)
Nee doushite tomaranai
Hey, why doesn't it stop?
Tomerannai rhythm ga
The rhythm that I can't stop
Karada no naka hibiiteiru
keeps reverberating through my body
Earphones kara nagareru melody dake ga
The melody playing in my earphones
Boku wo boku de isasete kureta
is the only thing that lets me be who I am
Akairo ni somaru sora
The sky is tinged in red
Boku no kokoro wa naniiro nan darou
But what color is my soul?
Oshiete
Boku wa doko e mukaeba ii?
Tell me
where should I go?
Zutto sagashiteita
I've always been searching
Taisetsu na nanika wo (hora!)
for something precious (hey!)
Itsuka nakushite shimau mono bakari nara
If everything's going to be lost some day
Tsuyoku kizande okou (ima!)
let's engrave it as deep as we can (now!)
Mijime na yoru mo baka warai mo
My most pathetic nights
and cackling laughter
Ano ne, sono ato de ienakatta hi mo
And days when I couldn't say
more than "You know..."
Ooh
(I'm alive now, yeah Springtime of life)
Nariyamanakute nani ga warui
What's wrong with not
letting my sound die down?
Seishun de nani ga warui
What's wrong with being young?
(Wow, wow, yeah!)
(Wow, wow)