(wow wow wow wow)
yatto minna aeta ne
It's time for us to meet at last
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
Don't stop! No, don't stop till the finish!
(wo oho oho oh)
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
Don't stop! No, don't stop till the finish!
(wo oho oho oh)
takatatta zenryoku hashirita
Bada bum bum, wanna run at full speed
shiba to suna to kimi no oikiri menyuu
Across turf, across dirt, breezing through your training menu
Turn up!
(Turn up!)
Turn up! (Turn up!)
koe dase sakebe
Let it all out, scream 'n shout
(wo oho oho oh)
toresen! fai! (oh!) fai! (oh!)
Tracen! Fight! Fight!
takatatta zenryoku agari taimu
Bada bum bum, all out for those final fractions
yuzurenai yume no tochuu
Can't stop dreaming only halfway through
(wow wow)
hajimeyou kokokara saikou story
Come on, let's go, here begins our epic story
(wow wow wow)
(oh o o oh oh o)
(oh oh o o oh oh ah)
akogare no chi e
To that place that seemed so far
(yuuki sukoshi karite)
(With a little push on the back)
katari atta memory
All of our shared memories
(nido to kinai ima o)
(Never let the moment slip away)
mou dokidoki mo tokimeki mo
Oh, this beating of my heart, fluttering with joy
osaerarenai tamannai
Can't keep it down, no, can't hold it back
atsui hara hara ga tomaranai
Rush of heat and passion, it's not gonna stop
kimi to hashiri kisoi gooru mezashi
You and I, running and racing toward our goal
haru ka hibike todoke music
Ringing out far and wide, it's our music
zutto zutto zutto zutto omoi
On and on and on and on, I dreamed
yume ga kitto kanau nara
If I could make them all come true now
ano hi kimi ni kanjita
Then I'll choose to believe in you
nanika o shinjite
That something I felt that day
haru mo natsu mo aki mo fuyu mo
Whether it's springtime or summer or autumn or winter
koe negai kogare hashire
Burn with hope and ambition and run
ah shouri e
Ah, to victory
Don't stop! No, don't stop 'til finish!!
Don't stop! No, don't stop till the finish!