ikimasu
Ready!
watashi no kokoro wa choko korone
My Heart is a Chocolate Cornet!
sotto mimi ni ateru to
Softly brushing across my ear
kikoeru kokoro no nami oto
A gentle sound from my heart can be heard
tokimeki ni amai kaori ga
The throbbing of a sweet smell
mune wo zawazawa sawagaseru no~
Pounding out from my chest
gyutto tsumatta watashi no omoi
Do you know all of the the emotions
kimi wa shitteru?~
That are packed deep within me?
choppiri nigai hi mo aru keredo
There may be some days that are a bit bitter
douka watashi wo~ ukeirete…?
When I wonder, will I be accepted...?
watashi no kokoro wa choko korone~
My heart is a chocolate cornet
hitokuchi kajireba afurechau!
Just a single bite, and it'll overflow!
ironna kimochi ga hajikechau!
All of my feelings are bursting out!
watashi no kokoro wa dokidoki ne~
My heart is beating fast
bitaasuiito ni urahara na
A taste that isn't far from bittersweet
kimi to kanaderu korunetto wa~
You and the cornet that you play
yukkuri taisetsu ni~ kanjita no~
Gently impart that sensation to me