itsumo to chigau nakama kakomu mooningu taimu
Morning time with unusual friends
kitto itsumo yori mo tanoshii kamo ne
Things will surely be more fun than usual
kokyuu awasetara
When our breathing aligns
hitotsu ni nareru ne
We can become as one
shinjiaeru kono kimochi wa
And believe that these feelings will
jikuu wo koeteku
Cross space and time
our Re:lation
Our Re:lation
thank you for your smile
Thank you for your smile
chigau basho demo
Even in a different place
thank you for your smile
Thank you for your smile
tsunaide ikeru
We can connect and go on
watashitachi no egao de
With all of our smiles
sou kitto
That's right, with you
thank you and good bye
Thank you and goodbye
owaranai kara
This isn't the end, so
thank you and good bye
Thank you and goodbye
mata aeru yo
We'll meet again
tobikkiri no egao de
With extraordinary smiles
thank you my friends
Thank you my friends!