Itsumademo itsudemo tsutaetakute
There's something you need to know
Utai tsuzukete
Forever and always
Kimi to hashirou
We'll be singing right by your side
Motto!
Forever and forever more!
Wow wow wow　Wow wow wow
LIVE with a smile, smile!
Motto!
Forever and forever more!
Wow wow wow　Wow wow wow
LIVE with a smile, smile!
Saisho ni mita hikari
The light we saw at the very start
Te o nobashita toki ga
When we reached out towards it
Hajimari sa
That was when it all started
Yuuki wa doko dakke?
Where does our courage lie?
Bokura no naka!
Right here, within us!
Ima mo atsuku moeru
It burns hot even till this day
Wow wow wo
Yume o egakeba
If we sketch out our dreams
Ureshiku tsuraku tanoshiku odoru kokoro ga
Our hearts, dancing with happiness, pain, and sadness
Wow wow wo
Tomerarenai yo
Can never be stopped
Ikeru toko made itte shimaou yo
So let's set off, as far as we can possibly go
Kagayaki ga umareta ano kisetsu o
We've always been and will always be running through the seasons
Bokutachi wa zutto hashitteru
When the radiance within us first came to life
Itsumademo itsudemo tsutaetakute
There's something you need to know, forever and always
Omoi wa hitotsu
Our feelings will be one
Utai tsuzukeyou
So we'll continue singing
Wow wow wow　Wow wow wow
LIVE with a smile, smile!
Motto!
Forever and forever more!
Wow wow wow　Wow wow wow
LIVE with a smile, smile!
Ame no ato no niji
After the rain, a rainbow appears in the sky
Watatte mitai ne
Let's cross it together
Sora wa harebare to
Now that the skies are clear
Kibou no taiyou ga ashita no
Like how the sun shines down hope
Hoshi-tachi o terasu you ni aa
On the stars of tomorrow, ah
Sekai wa tsunagatteru
The world truly is connected as one
Wow wow wo
Yume wa nando mo
Our dreams will never disappear
Furuete yurete
No matter how many times
Soredemo kitto kienai yo
They quake and waver
Wow wow wo
Akiramenaide
We will not be giving up
Yaritai koto wa
We'll do everything
Yatte shimaunda
We've ever dreamed of doing
Kagayaki to ikiteru ima ikiteru
Our dreams and miracles
Bokutachi no yume to kiseki
They live alongside the radiance, they live in the now
Dokomademo doko demo oikaketai
No matter how far they seem, we'll chase after them, forever and always
Omoi wa onaji
We all feel the same way
Utai tsuzukeyou
So we'll continue singing
Inori no koe ga
The sounds of prayer
Utagoe ni naru
Turn into song
Kimi no negai wa
That wish of yours will come true
Itsuka
Someday
Kimi no chikara de
You'll make it
Kanau hi ga kurunda
Come true
Egao de ne saa susumou!
So put on a smile, we'll set off together!
Waratte norikoeyou
We'll overcome everything with a smile
Saa susumou!
So let's set off together!
Seinaru
We'll set off
Jounetsu de
With the sacred passion
Susumou yo
In your heart
Yume to deau tame ni
Let's sing until we meet
Utau yo
Our dreams for real
Saisho ni mita hikari
The light we saw at the very start
Te o nobashita
When we reached out towards it
Toki ga
That was
Hajimari dattanda
When it all started
La la la la la
Yuuki de
We'll change
La la la la la la
Mirai ga
The future
La la la　La la la　La la la　La la la
Kawaru
With our courage
Kawaru yo!
We'll definitely do it!
Kagayaki ga umareta ano kisetsu o
We've always been and will always be running through the seasons
Bokutachi wa zutto hashitteru
When the radiance within us first came to life
Itsumademo itsudemo tsutaetakute
There's something you need to know
Omoi wa hitotsu
Our feelings will be one
Utai tsuzukeyou
So we'll continue singing
Wow wow wow　Wow wow wow
LIVE with a smile, smile!
Motto!
Forever and forever more!
Wow wow wow　Wow wow wow
LIVE with a smile, smile!