kuraku semai no ga suki datta
I liked dark, cramped spaces,
fukak' kaburu FOOD no naka
so I'd bury my face deep in my hood
mujou na sekai wo uranda me wa
My eyes resented the heartless world,
dou shiyou mo nak' ai wo ho sh'teta
but yearned for love
ame ni nureru no ga suki datta
I liked being soaked by the rain,
kumotta kao ga niau kara
because my face looked better clouded over
arashi ni obieteru furi wo sh'te
I pretended to be afraid of the storm
sora ga wareru no wo matteitan da
while waiting for the sky to burst
kakinarase
Strum through the light's distortion
hikari no FUZZ de
raimei wo
I want to make thunder roar
todorokasetain da
uchinarase
Drum beyond the pain
hitami no saki he
dou shiyou
What can I do? This fierce
pounding is out of control
dai bousou doumou na kodou wo
kakinarase
Strum in a harmonizing quartet
majiwaru QUARTET
kak'mei wo
I want to cause a revolution
nash'togete mitai na
uchinarase
Drum in a lamenting forte
nageki no FORTE
dou shiyou
What can I do? My savage
nature is beyond wild
chou honpou kyoubou na honshou wo