rasuto chansu ni ueta tsumasaki ga
My toes, hungry for a last chance
odoridasu mama kaketa kono yozora
Began to dance across the night sky
nami no sutansu ja nabikanai
An ordinary stance will never enchant
hoshi wa houseki no akogare~
Only stars can be the envy of jewels
ukabu namida to ase wa chi no nagori
Tears and sweat float on the surface, the traces of blood
me no naka de shika oyogenakya shibai
To only swim in someone’s eyes is but a play
dakedo suteeji ga nigasanai
But the stage won’t let me go
itsu itsumademo akogare~
I’ll seek for it forevermore
kogareteiru yo~
Longing for it
(I’ve never seen (oh) such a liar.)
umaretsuki tatte no sokonashi
You must have been born with this level of depravity
(This lie is love. And this lie is a gift to the world.)
dare to ikita ka omoidashite~
Remember who you lived alongside
watashi ga inochi wo kakeru kara~
I’ll risk my life
ageru kara aa
I’ll give my life to you
anata wa jikan wo kureta no deshou?
After all, you gave me time, didn’t you?
arayuru nozomi no subete wo kanaetara aa
Once I fulfill all my desires
hatasetara aa
Once I achieve them
anata ni aitai
I want to see you
hoshi ni negai wo kakete~
So I wish upon a star
saa hoshi no kotachi yo~ yoku o nemuri nasai
Come, children of the stars, sleep well
kagayaki wa niburanai anata-tachi~ naraba
The light will not dim, if you’re the ones who shine
saa hoshi no kotachi yo~ yoku o nemuri nasai
Come, children of the stars, sleep well