Chan × Chan
Ai!! Chiki chiki ban ban
Ai?! Chiki chiki chan chan
Aa! Chiki chiki ban ban
Ai!! Chuki chuki chuki ban ban
High chiki chiki ban ban
Ai?! Chiki chiki chan chan
Aa! Chiki chiki ban ban
Ai!! Chuki chuki
Neko mo shakushi mo
Everyone and his brother
minna kimagure de tsurai
Is fickle and it's so trying
Yoeba tequila
If you get drunk on tequila
Aranu mousou renzoku de pikan
With a string of groundless fantasies, flash
Yume wa Pandora
Dreams are Pandora
Hora, aketakunaru
Can'tcha feel the urge to open 'em?
Minna kitaishite, party people
Expect good things from everybody, party people
Konya Fujiyama noboranya wakaranai
You won't understand unless you climb Mt. Fuji tonight
Kessen wa shuumatsu no shukumei
The showdown is the destiny of the weekend
Chan × Chan
Ai!! Chiki chiki ban ban
Nanimo mottaiburazu tanoshime
Enjoy yourself without being pretentious about anything
Fever tonight
Chan × Chan
Ai?! Chiki chiki ban ban
Nando mushakusha shitatte,
No matter how often you're irritated,
Party tonight
party tonight
Chan × Chan
Aa! Chiki chiki ban ban
Orokamono hodo high to kasu kanzen shakai
A perfect society where the stupider you act, the greater the high
Chan × Chan
Ai!! Chiki chiki ban ban
Minna superstar no tamago sa,
Everybody is a superstar in the making,
Diva tonight
diva tonight