Vesnianochka, vesnianochka,
Oh Spring song, Spring song
De ty zymuvala?
Where have you spent your Winter?
U sadochku na klenochku
In the garden, sitting on a maple tree
Sorochechku priala
You’ve been spinning a shirt.
Tam u lisi na yuzlisi
There on the edge of a forest
Sova v vodu duye
An owl is blowing into the water.
Zaspivayu spivanochku
I’ll sing a song -
Nehay vona chuye.
Let her hear it.
Zapletysia, shume, barvinochkom,
Shum, get twined with periwinkle
Ya tobi spivayu vesnianochku
I’m singing the spring song to you.
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu konopelechky
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing hemp plants,
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu zelenesenki
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing green ones.
Pryidy, pryidy, vesnianochko
Come Spring, come
Ta y ne zabarysia
Don’t wait around
A my vyidem na yulytsiu
We’ll go outside
Budem lyubytysia
to love each other.
Vesnianochko, panianochko
Oh Spring, our Miss,
Zahlian u vikontse
Look in our window.
Zaspivaly spivanochku
We had sang our song
Zasvitylo sontse
And the Sun shined on.
Numo, numo zapletemo shuma
Come on, come on, let’s twine the Shum,
Zapletemo, huliaty pidemo
Twine the Shum, dance it around.
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu konopelechky
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing hemp plants,
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu zelenesenki
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing green ones.
Zapletysia, shume, zapletysia
Shum, get twined, get twined!
Barvinochkom, shume, zastelysia
Shum, get spread with periwinkle.
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu konopelechky
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing hemp plants,
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu zelenesenki
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing green ones.
Vesnianochka, vesnianochka
Oh Spring song, Spring song
De ty zymuvala?
Where have you spent your Winter?
U sadochku na klenochku
In the garden, sitting on a maple tree
Sorochechku priala
You’ve been spinning a shirt.
Oy u lisi na yuzlisi
There on the edge of a forest
Sova v vodu duye
An owl is blowing into the water.
Zaspivayu spivanochku
I’ll sing a song -
Nehay vona chuye.
Let her hear it.
Zapletysia, shume, barvinochkom,
Shum, get twined with periwinkle
Ya tobi spivayu vesnianochku
I’m singing the spring song to you.
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu konopelechky
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing hemp plants,
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu zelenesenki
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing green ones.
Numo, numo narobyly shuma,
Come on, come on, we’ve made some noise.
Narobyly, vesnu rozbudyly,
Made some noise and awoke the Spring.
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu konopelechky
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing hemp plants,
Siyu, siyu, siyu, siyu zelenesenki.
Sowing, sowing, sowing, sowing green ones.