Polamgattu Dhummulona
Like an aggressive bull
jumping in the dust of the fields
Potla Gittha Dhookinattu
Poleramma Jatharalo
Like the main dancer dancing
at the festival of a local goddess
Potharaju Ooginattu
Kirruseppulu Esukoni
Like playing with the stick
while wearing wooden slippers
Karrasamu Sesianattu
Marrisettu Needalona
Like a bunch of young boys
gathering in the shade of a banyan tree
Kurragumpu Koodinattu
Yerrajonna Rottelona
Like eating a roti jowar with a chilli
Mirapathokku Kalipinattu
Na Pata Soodu
Listen to my song
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu Veera Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu, Crazy Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu Oora Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu, Wild Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Pachi Mirapalaga Picha Naatu
Naatu like a green chili
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Vichu Katthi Laga Verri Naatu
Naatu like a sharp dagger
Gundeladhiri Poyela
Like beating a drum
that makes your heart beat faster
Dandanakara Moginattu
Sevulu Sillu Padelaga
Like the shrill voice of a bird
that can ring your ears
Keesu Pitta Koosinattu
Yelu Sitikalesela
Like singing a song that can make
your fingers snap to the beat
Yavaram Saginattu
Kalu Sindhu Thokkela
Like the wild dance
when there's a fast beat
Dhummaram Reginattu
Vollu Sematapattela
Like the dance
that makes your body sweat
Veerangam Sesinattu~
Na Pata Soodu
Listen to my song
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu Veera Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu, Crazy Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu Oora Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu, Wild Naatu
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Gadda Paralaga Chedda Naatu
Naatu like a green chili
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Ukkapotha Laga Thikka Naatu
Naatu like a sharp dagger
(Dugu Dugu Dugu Dugu Hey Hey)
Bhoomi Dhaddharillela
Dance so that the blood in your body
Vontiloni Ragathamantha
Rankelesi Yegirela
Jump violently which will shake the earth
Yesero Yakayeki
Naatu Naatu Naatu
(Vaha)
(Yesko)
Are Dhummu Dhummu Dhulipela
The life force inside of you should dance with joy
Lopalunna Panamantha
Dumuku Dumuku Ladela
So jump until the dust rises in the air
Dhookero Sarasari
Naatu Naatu Naatu
Naa~tu
Naa~tu Naa~tu
Naa~tu~~
Naa~tu Naa~tu Naa~tu~~
Naa~tu Naa~tu Naa~tu~~~
(Hey! Adhi)
(Kanakara Kanakara Hey Hey Hey Hey)
(Kanakara Nakara Nakara)
(Nakara Nakara Nakara Nakara)
Naa~tu Naa~tu Naa~tu~~
Naa~tu Naa~tu Naa~tu~~~
(Hey!)