burning parappa gao
Burning parappa roar
howling parappa gao
Howling parappa roar
growing parappa gao
Growing parappa roar
loving parappa gao
(uh yeah)
Loving parappa roar
(Uh yeah)
super chorogons
super easy dragons
chorokutatte zenzen kamaimasen
It's perfectly all right to be small.
tsugou ii no ga nanika warui desuka
Have you considered the advantages?
itsudatte shoemotarasetemo
It's how you carry yourself that matters.
yuuretsu nante imi nakunacchauyo
It's not a competition, after all!
hiyashite
Don't worry about it.
(ganbatte)
netsubou shichau
(Do your best!)
Burn with desire.
(kenka shite)
chisaii sekai yorimo
(Fight!)
This small world
chikaku ni aru kokoro ga ne
that brought our hearts closer together
hane datte nobaseru
also gave us a place of pure warmth
kiyoku attakai basho
to spread our wings and fly!
minna de issho ni irukara soredake de ii
We're all together and that's all we need to be
meido, meido, meido with our hearts
made, made, made with our hearts!
peaceful na taikutsu wa
Any peaceful tedium we find
ippai, ippai odoshiyouyo
will be chased far, far way.
umareta toki kara sou datta koto wa
The circumstances we're born into
minna, minna, minna chigaunda ne
are unique for each and every single one of us.
kamiawanai kachikan mo
Tear into those discrepancies
kamitsubushichaimashou
and grind them to bits
doragon zu
as dragon's do!
burning parappa gao
Burning parappa roar
howling parappa gao
Howling parappa roar
gao
Roar!