Kotoba harari
Words silently float down, I start to feel lighter
Kimochi fuwari
Noseru omoi-tachi
As my feelings begin to take shape
Koi ni somatteku
It looks like love's in the air
Kimi to itara
It feels as though the rain is more calming than ever
Ame no naka mo chigatta shizuku ni naru
Whenever I'm with you
Donna moji wo tsuzuttara
Which are the words I need to write out
Iroasezu ni nokoru no desho?
To make them last and for them to never fade?
Shitteru nda
If nothing changes, this'll be nothing more than a distant memory
Ima no futari wa tooi ano hi ni naru koto
Sou deshou kami-sama
Isn't that right, God?
Marumaru mizu mo konai densha mo
The moment before a droplet breaks, or before the train comes
Motto kono shunkan da
I pray they will never end
Douka eien ni tsuzuite
"Please let it go on forever"
Nante muri ka na?
Is that too much to ask?