Itsumo BA-RI-BA-RI-BA-RI tachimukatte
Always BA-RI-BA-RI-BA-RI Stand up to it
(Hang in there!!)
GI-RI-GI-RI-GI-RI kuishibatte
GI-RI-GI-RI-GI-RI clench your teeth
(Hang in there!!)
Ima wo ikiru chikara
The power to live in the moment
Special Force
(Special Force…)
Dareshimo motteru Power
Everybody's got Power
(Power)
Shirazushirazu ni kagi kakete
Unknowingly locked away
Kimi wa yuumou kakan na Flower
You are a brave and daring Flower
(Flower)
Rifujin to kyou mo tatakatte
Fighting the unreasonable today
Asa wa mezamashi to no koubousen
In the morning it's a battle against the alarm
Gozen wa kikakusho to kaigi de shinrisen
In the morning it's a mind game of proposals and meetings
Zettai ni makenai kimi nara daijoubu
You'll never lose, you're gonna be okay
(It’s gonna be ok!!)
Ganbaru kimi wa toutoi
You're doing your best
Kitto mukuwareru hi ga kuru darou
I'm sure the day will come when you'll be rewarded
Sono chikara Wake up shinjite Do it again
Wake up and believe in your power Do it again
Daremo ga tokubetsu na Only one, Let’s go!!
Everyone is special, Only one, Let's go!
Itsumo BA-RI-BA-RI-BA-RI tachimukatte
Always BA-RI-BA-RI-BA-RI Stand up to it
(Hang in there!!)
GI-RI-GI-RI-GI-RI kuishibatte
GI-RI-GI-RI-GI-RI clench your teeth
(Hang in there!!)
Kimi wa “zettai akiramenai” sore ga chikara sa taisetsu na Special Force
You'll never give up. That's your strength, your precious Special Force.
Kyou mo BA-RI-BA-RI-BA-RI tsukisusunde
Today too, BA-RI-BA-RI-BA-RI
(Hang in there!!)
GI-RI-GI-RI-GI-RI norikoete
GI-RI-GI-RI-GI-RI Get over it
(Hang in there!!)
ikou yo Stronger
Let's go, Stronger
Kimi no utsukushii Special Force
Your beautiful Special Force