aimai na kaiketsu dou mogaitemo
The solution is vague, no matter how I may struggle
tanjun mondai kaitou naraba
My only way to answer a simple problem
omote ura tsukaikitte
Is to exhaust all possible options
toozakaru renshuu kurikaesu no
And practice distancing myself, again and again
Haze Haseru Haterumade
(Rushing Onward Until The End)
aitai wa yuugen kowasanai you ni
The desire to see you is something limited, so I try to keep it intact
tashikamete shimau kuse wo
I develop a habit of checking in on it
iyagaranaide mou tasukete yo
But don’t let it bother you, just come save me
mata supairaru ni karamaru
I’m about to get caught in another spiral
mou kimi dokoro ja nai yo
This problem already exists beyond you
haru mo shoudoku mo owarasetai kara
I want to put an end to this spring season, this sterilization
jinkou chinou tsukatte hikitometari shinaide
Don’t try to hold me back with common sense
kantan ni seikai baramakanaide ite ne
Don’t go effortlessly throwing around accepted truths
oyogu hitsuyou mo kizu mo nai no ni naze ka
I have no scars, no reason to swim
oboeta ikitsugi wo shite
But I’ve learned how to manage my breathing anyway
saki ni oboreru yo sore de keshikireru nara
I’ll go ahead and drown first, if that puts an end to all of this
doko made mo tada tooku e
Moving endlessly onward, far far away
kireigoto iu yo kachi wo nezuketa mama
I’ll speak an old truism, value judgement and all
oide tte oide tte oide tte nande
“Come on over, come one over, come on over!” Why?
ashita ni wa mou wasurete shimau no ni…
I’ll have forgotten it all by tomorrow anyway
kimi no ketten bakari asatte
I go looking for only your bad parts
koritsu muen no wana wo mogutte
I fight on in the trap known as loneliness and isolation
fukai sousou ni mizukara oborete
Drowning in my own deep sense of honor
suzushii kao de waratte
Why do you laugh so effortlessly
sotto namida wo kobosu no nande
While your tears fall softly?
wataritakunai no ni doushite
Why? When I’m trying so hard to not give in
zurui yo zurui yo
It’s unfair, it’s unfair
itai itai no tonde ike tte
Oh, pain, pain, fly away!
mou ii yo mou ii yo
Just forget about it, forget about it
kimi no imi ni narenai nara
If I can’t be the meaning in your life
joushou kiryuu ubatte hikitometari shinaide
Don’t try to hold me back by stealing my updraft
kantan ni kanousei ataenaide ite ne
Don’t go effortlessly presenting me possibilities
oyogu hitsuyou mo kizu mo nai no ni naze ka
I have no scars, no reason to swim
oboeta ikitsugi wo shite
But I’ve learned how to manage my breathing anyway
saki ni oboreru yo sore de keshikireru nara
I’ll go ahead and drown first, if that puts an end to all of this
doko made mo tada tooku e
Moving endlessly onward, far far away
kireigoto iu yo kachi wo nezuketa mama
I’ll speak an old truism, value judgement and all
oide tte oide tte oide tte nande
“Come on over, come one over, come on over!” Why?
ashita ni wa mou wasurete shimau no ni…
I’ll have forgotten it all by tomorrow anyway
nani ga aragau no? nani wo nikumeru no?
What opposes me? What can I possibly hate?
azukenaide ite yo
Don’t leave these answers up to me!
oyogu hitsuyou mo kizu mo nai no ni naze ka
I have no scars, no reason to swim
oboeta ikitsugi wo shite
But I’ve learned how to manage my breathing anyway
saki ni oboreru yo yubi de keshikireru nara
I’ll go ahead and drown first, if I can swipe it all away with just one finger
doko made mo tada tooku e
Moving endlessly onward, far far away
kireigoto iu yo kachi wo nezuketa mama
I’ll speak an old truism, value judgement and all
oide tte oide tte oide tte nande
“Come on over, come one over, come on over!” Why?
ashita ni wa mou nogarete shimau no ni
I’ll have made my escape by tomorrow
atehamattetemo aragatteitai yo
Even if I’m doing what’s expected, I want to keep struggling
koyoi mo mizu ni tokete oyasumi
Tonight, I’ll melt into the water once more, bidding goodnight
batsu ga attetemo furimukanai yo
Even if punishment awaits, I won’t look back
tanjun ni shinchou ni oyoide itai no
I want to swim on, simply, with purpose
atehamattetemo aragatteitai yo
Even if I’m doing what’s expected, I want to keep struggling
koyoi mo mizu ni tokete oyasumi
Tonight, I’ll melt into the water once more, bidding goodnight
doromamire demo shinjisasete yo
Even if I’m covered in mud, make me believe
kotonaru jibun wo aishite itai no
I want to love myself for being so different