La la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la
Saa konya mo genki ni hajimemashou!
Alright, let's get fired up and get started again tonight!
Tenshi ga maioriru jikan
It's time for these angels to fly down
Jiyuu kimama ni hashaideitai no
We want to frolic as much as we want
Issho ni asobimasho!
Let's play together!
Mainichi iroiro to aru kedo kyou wa zenbu poipoi poipoi!
We've got a lot of worries everyday but let's throw, throw, throw'em all away today!
Minna de odorou ryoute wo hiroge ima
Let's all open our arms, and dance together, right now
Anata no sugu soba ni iru yo
We're right by your side
Kimama na tenshitachi
These carefree angels
Amefuri sabishii toki ni wa
When it rains and you feel lonely
Egao de te wo tatakou!
Let's clap our hands with a smile!
Anata no sugu soba ni iru yo
We're right by your side
Tsurai toki, kanashii toki
When you're having a hard time, when you're sad
Ohoshisama kirakira egao de
With our smiles twinkling like the stars
Ashita wa hare moyou
Tomorrow's gonna be a sunny day
Dokidoki wo purezento
We'll give you the present of heart-pounding
Koko dake no himitsu da yo!
It's a secret just between us!