aishita riyuu mo wasurechatte
I’ve forgotten why I loved you.
kashoku kimi no mune de naichatte
I’ve cried in my voracious chest.
hada no iro sura mienakunatteiru
I can’t even remember the color of your skin anymore.
jibun dake kizutsuita tsumori de
Certain that I’m the only one who got hurt
warui no wa dareka da to omotte
I think “whose fault is this, really!?”
ashi ga nukeochita no mo kizukanai
Without even noticing my legs giving out.
yume ya kibou wa nan datta?
What about my hopes and dreams?
yaritai koto wa kore datta?
Was this who I wanted to become?
kako ga bokura wo matteiru
The past is just waiting.
donyoku na kao de matteiru
Eagerly, with a greedy smile, it waits.
wabishisa mo
If it weren’t for
kanashimi mo nakereba
That loneliness and sadness,
yoru ga shinu tabi
I wouldn’t have sung
uta nante utawanakatta
Every time the night died.
anata no egao ga koko ni aru nara
If your smile had been here,
akirame nante shinakattan da
Then I never would have given up.
anata no kotoba wo omoidasu kara
Remembering your words was enough.
nagusame nante iranakatta
I didn’t need more comforting than that.
ikiru imi bakari omoidasu kara
I can think of nothing but the meaning of my life,
yasashisa wo tsune ni utagatta
And so I doubt any sign of kindness, always.
anata no namida wo mite waraetara
I realize now now what a shameless person I would’ve been,
imasara haji nado shiranakatta
If I had laughed at your tears.
uguisu ga naite
As the Uguisu sang
yaburisuteta sotsugyou shousho ga
The graduation certificate I tore to pieces
yozora ni natte mattetta
Fluttered and danced across the night sky.
kako wo kuraitsukushita
I’ve devoured the past until nothing remained.
hankou ki da to utomareta kodomo tachi wa fukushuu ni hashiri
Children, shunned for rebelling, are out for revenge
imi ni sugaru funuketa otona tachi wa uta wo utaitagaru
While cowardly adults that cling to their meaning are eager to sing.
wakasa wo shiite musaboru damin
The violent thirst for youth idly slumbers.
kizukeba tsume ga hagareochiru
By the time they realize, their nails will be peeling off.
ame ga suki datta riyuu mo
I’ve completely forgotten my favorite songs
suki na uta mo wasuresatta
Or the reason I loved the rain.
kokoro ni hibiku no wa mono bakari
The only thing that moves my heart now are things.
sore na no ni hito ga koishikutte
But even so, I can’t help but long for company.
anata e no kimochi dake
My feelings for you
ima mo owaranain da
Are the only thing that still lingers.
tatoeba bokura ga machi de deatte
Say we happened to meet somewhere by chance.
yume no you na hanashi wo tsumugetara
If I could spin a dream-like story,
anata to boku wa
Then maybe you and I
waraeru darou ka
Would be able to laugh together.
gamen no naka de anata ni aetara
But if we met through the screen,
omoidasu no wa koukai bakari da
We’d think back on it with only regret.
ima demo itoshii yo
But still, I think back fondly on our time.
ano koro ni ima mo modoritai yo
I wish we could return there.
konna otona de gaman dekitara
If I had been this mature and patient back then,
kurushimi nante shiranakatta
Then I’d never have had to experience this pain.
kotoba de subete kaiketsu suru nara
If words could have resolved everything,
koko made namida wa denakatta
Then I wouldn’t have cried so much.
anata ga atama de uzu wo maku kara
I still hated those mornings
ima mo kono asa ga kirai datta
Because of how you swirled in my head.
otona ni naru no ga kowakatta
Becoming an adult felt scary.
tsuyoku naru koto ga kowakatta
Growing up felt scary.
uguisu ga naite
As the Uguisu cries
gomi ni natta seifuku ga
The ragged school uniform
yozora ni natte mattetta
Fluttered away into the night sky
kako wo kuraitsukushita
I’ve devoured the past until nothing remained.