sugiru dake no jikan ja kuyashii
It's frustrating how time does nothing but elapse
kizamanakucha
I have to count the passing minutes
koko ni iru to kokoro ga sakebu shunkan
The moment you are with me my heart screams out
I'm dreaming
mayoi nagara namida wo nomikonda
I swallowed my tears when I was lost
bukiyou da ne yume mo toomawari
I'm clumsy right? I get lost in my dreams
oozora wo miage nanimo iezu
Looking up at the sky without saying a word
mune ga itamu wake kangaeteita
I wondered why my heart was aching
DAYS of DASH
kaze wo hashirinukete
Keep on running through the wind
kimi to boku no naka de nani ga hajimatta no darou
What has started inside you and me?
wakaranai kedo
I don't understand it
kirakira hikaru taiyou ga terasu basho wo
Let's continue to head towards the place
zutto susumou
where the brightly sparkling sun shines
eien nado shiranai keredo
Even though we will never understand
tsuyokunai yo dakara mae wo mukun da
I'm not strong, that's why I always looked ahead
aseri tsutsu mo
In my impatience
tobira akete tobidashite mitai shoudou
I had the urge to open the door and fly out
afuredashita kanjou dakishime
Embracing my overflowing feelings
kowakunai yo tomo ni iru kagiri
I'm not scared, as long as you are here
aozora ni nageta atsui kibou
There is no way that I will give up
akirameru nante arienai yo
on my warm hopes that escaped into the sky
EYES to EYES
kotoba iranai sekai
Right now our world is starting
kimi to boku no sekai ima ga hajimatta no darou
A world where words aren't needed
wakarikaketeru
I'm beginning to understand
mirai wo saguru kakugo kimeta totan
The second we decide to explore the future
motto kawaru
It changes even more
eien e no tsunagari sagashitai
I want to search for the connection to eternity
motto…
More and more
oozora wo miage nanimo iezu
Looking up at the sky without saying a word
mune ga itamu wake kangaeteita
I wondered why my heart was aching
DAYS of DASH
kaze wo hashirinukete
Keep on running through the wind
kimi to boku no naka de nani ga hajimatta no darou
What has started inside you and me?
wakaranai kedo
I don't understand it
kirakira hikaru taiyou ga terasu basho wa doko ni
Where is the place where the brightly sparkling sun shines?
nani wo hajimeyou to shiteru?
What are you trying to start?
I'm a dreamer
mou kotoba iranai sekai
Right now our world is starting
kimi to boku no sekai ima ga hajimatta no darou
A world where words aren't needed anymore
wakarikaketeru
I'm beginning to understand
mirai wo saguru kakugo kimeta totan
The second we decide to explore the future
motto kawaru
It changes even more
eien nado shiranai keredo
Even though we will never understand