Yoru no aima wo nuu you ni
Like a fish skimming along a moonlit ocean.
Hashiru densha no naka yurari
Ran the train gently swaying from side to side.
Ushiromuki ni nagareru keshiki wo hitori
Looking out, the scenery is quickly
slipping by and then there's me,
Suwatte miteita miteita
just out there, a pair of eyes, a pair of eyes.
Hirusagari no hizashi wa
The waning evening, dyed in orange light
Yuuhi no orenji iro ni somatte
and ruled over by the setting sun. I saw it
Aiiro no sora ni oshi tsubusarete iku
swallowed up and buried in the overwhelming indigo sky.
Sono saigo no hikari wo oshimu you ni
I had to run after the last ray of
Me de oikaketa no wa
shining light chasing a memory
Kyou de baibai dakara
because now it's goodbye.
Ashita wo suteru tame ni tobidashita touhikou
I'm leaving on a journey to abandon
tomorrow far away.
Katamichi bun no kippu de ikeru toko made iku no
Bought a one-way ticket and
decided to go far as I can go.
Doko ni mo ibasho nante nai watashi wo kono mama
There's no place where I belong right now,
so I'll just lose myself in the night,
Yoru ni oitette oitette
in the night.
Adrift
Fui ni mado kara mieta keshiki ga kurayami ni
All of a sudden, all the window shown before me was dark.
Kizuita are wa sou da kitto yoru no umi
And then I knew what I saw must be the view of the night sea.
Dekigokoro ni te wo hikarete orita umibe no machi
On a whim I stopped by a beach town,
driven on. By unknown forces.
Nami no oto ni tada michibikareru you ni aruku
Waves guiding my way, or maybe
Dareka ni yobareru you ni
someone was calling my soul
Chikazuita umi no hotori
to the seashore.
Koko ni wa hitori
Now that I'm alone
Mou kono mama isso karada wo koko ni
I think this could very well end up being my home and resting place.
Nante kangaeteita watashi no mae ni
Imagining all what I would do,
Totsuzen arawareta kimi wa
you suddenly called to me out of the blue.
Tsukiakari no shita
Under the bright moonlight, pale-skinned and ghostly fair
Aojiroi hada
Shiro no wan piisu
in a white one-piece dress.
“konna toko de nani shiteiru no?”
"What are you doing here at this time of night?",
Nante kyuu ni tazuneru kara
you asked me with an inspecting glance.
Kotoba ni tsumari nagara
I'll try and keep it short for you,
“umi wo, mi ni”
"I'm here for the sea."
Kimi wa nanika wo toridashita
After that you took out from behind your back
Sore wa sukoshi furui hanabi setto
a long unused set of fireworks for play.
Soko de kizuita
That's when I saw and noticed
Kanojo wa konkuriito no ue
you were walking barefoot on the concrete.
Hadashi datta
You didn't care.
Kyou de zenbu owari ni suru to kimeta kara
I had decided this day would be the one I'd end it all for good.
Kitto watashi ga ano sekai ni chikazuita kara
So maybe I'm already gone and have stumbled into the underworld.
Miete shimatta deatte shimatta
Maybe this meeting's just an apparition
Sonna kimi to futari de
but this night, together we went and
Hanabi no fuu wo kitta
lit those antique fireworks.
Nakanaka tsukanai hanabi ni hi wo chikazuke nagara
As hard as I tried my firework wouldn't light,
so you got closer to share the flame
Watashi ga koko ni kita wake wo kimi wa atete miseta
and rightly guessed my reason and motive for being here so far from home.
Soshite nandomo yame na yo tte
You kept on encouraging me and urging not to go through with it,
Shinken na manazashi de itta
"please don't do it."
Dakedo…
Sono shunkan kono te no saki de hikari ga hajiketa
"But I..."
And that's when a dazzling burst of light came from my hand.
Omowazu “tsuita!” to futari de soroete sakendeta
The firework was ignited and we both jumped up
and screamed "it's lit!"
Kore demo ka to kagayaku hibana no
The loud, crackling firework broke through the night air shining and dazzling
Surudoi oto ga hibiita hibiita
sinking deep in my senses
in my senses.
Yukkuri nagameru hima mo naku kiete iku kagayaki wo
Shining bright and intense before us
but then dimming and fading as quickly as it came.
Mottai nakute saigo no isshun made oikaketa
Before I could burn the sight into my eyes,
again I'd be left in darkness.
Densha no mado kara mieta
I'd chase it desperately
Saigo no taiyou wo oshinda you ni
like the twilight evening on my train to nowhere
Oikaketa
into nothing.
Yappari watashi
I just can't. I'd end it.
Nee yoru ga aketara kimi wa
Hey, tell me the answer to this one question.
Dokoka e kiete shimau no ka na
Are you going to disappear when the morning comes?
Yoru no tobari wo nukedashite
Finally I walked right past the curtain of night.
Asa no hikari de me ga sameta
Waking up, rubbing my eyes with the morning light.
Tonari wo miru to atarimae no you ni nemuru
To the side I looked and there, as if nothing important just happened.
Kimi no sugata
You were lying there.