fushigi da ne ima no kimochi~
This feeling, it's strange, isn't it?
sora kara futte kita mitai~
It's almost as though it came fluttering down from the sky
tokubetsu na kisetsu no iro ga~ tokimeki o miseru yo~
The color of this special season fills me with excitement
hajimete~ deatta toki kara
From the moment we met,
yokan ni sawagu~ kokoro no melody
The melody of my heart has been ringing with premonitions
tomerarenai tomaranai~ naze~
It can’t be stopped, it won’t be stopped — why?
todokete
Ring out
setsunasa ni wa~ namae o~ tsukeyou ka "snow halation"
Shall I name this heart-rending pain "Snow halation"?
omoi ga kasanaru made~ matezu ni~
I can’t wait for our feelings to resonate
kuyashii kedo suki tte junjou
It’s frustrating, but it’s a pure-hearted devotion called love
binetsu no naka~ tameratte mo dame da ne~
Even in this mild fever, I can’t hesitate
tobikomu yuuki ni sansei~ mamonaku start~!!
I'll accept the courage to dive in; it's about to start!
oto mo naku kehai mo naku~
Without a sound, nor a sign
shizuka ni unmei wa kawaru~
Our fate changes silently
korekara no mirai ni mune no~ kodou ga hayaku naru~
At the thought of the coming future, my heartbeat quickens
tatoeba~ komatta toki ni wa
When you feel troubled
sugu kaketsukete~ dakishimetakute
I’ll come running right away, wanting to hug you tightly,
doko ni ite mo dokodemo~ fly high
Wherever you are, no matter where, I'll Fly high!
isoide
Hurry up
itsu no ma ni ka~ ookiku~ nari sugita "true emotion"
Before I knew it, my true emotions grew too large to contain
yume dake miteru you ja~ tsurai yo~
It's painful to never do more than dream of it
koibito wa kimi tte iitai
I want you to be mine!
yasashii me ga~ tomadotteru iya da yo~
I don't want to be bewildered by your gentle eyes
kono mama ikki ni aijou~ azukete please!!
Accept all my love for you as it is, Please!
todokete
Ring out
setsunasa ni wa~ namae o~ tsukeyou ka "snow halation"
Shall I name this heart-rending pain "Snow halation"?
omoi ga kasanaru made~ matezu ni~
I can’t wait for our feelings to resonate
kuyashii kedo suki tte junjou~
It’s frustrating, but it’s a pure-hearted devotion called love
binetsu no naka~ tameratte mo dame da ne~
Even in this mild fever, I can’t hesitate
tobikomu yuuki ni sansei~ mamonaku start~!!
I'll accept the courage to dive in; it's about to start!