fumitsukerareta kodoku to PEDAL kara
The tune that plays when my loneliness
and the pedal are stepped on
nandomo narihibiku neiro ga hoho ni tsutau
Tracks down my cheeks over and over again
uchitsukerareta kodoku ni
The pounding of my loneliness
SNAR' no RHYTHM ga kasanatte
Is joined by the rhythm of the snare drum
tashika na kodou ni naru
To create a solid pulse
dareka kokoro no NOISE wo totte
Someone, please remove
the distortion on my heart
watashi wo nozo'te yo
And take a look inside me
daremo kokoro no ok' ni wa~ irenai keredo
Nobody can get inside my heart
kitai shite shimau sonna yoru
But it's the kind of night
when I hope someone will
DISTORTION IT'S MOTION
Distortion it's Motion
hajimattara mou tomaranai
Once it starts, there's no stopping it
seigen mo keiken de nurikaerareru sa
Limits can be overwritten with experience
sou darou
Isn't that right?
DISTORTION IT'S MOTION
Distortion is always like that
sanou oikoshite kokoro ga hashiridasu
My heart takes off, outpacing my left brain
kimi no tsugi no oto ni ESCORT
Toward where you are
An escort to the next note
hibi no urei ni DISTORTION
Distortion on my day-to-day anguish
hitori no yor' narasu CHORD
The chord I play when I'm alone at night
kimi mo onaj' kai?
Is it the same for you?
risouzou oikaketa hibi
I spent all those days chasing my ideal image
F CHORD kakinarasun da DISTORTION
Play an F chord with distortion
VOLUME~ wo furikiru yo
So loud that the needle swings off the scale