dil nachda re dil nachda
The heart is twirling! The heart is twirling!
khulke thirakne se bachda
If you can, resist the urge to get lost in the dance.
Ready!
dekh!
Look!
himmat se naacho
My buddies dance with passion and groove.
thirak thirak yaaron
dharti hila do
Make the clouds dance with you;
make the sky come and dance with you.
thirak thirak re
maati ka baadal
ufak ufak jaaye
ambar jhuka do
thirak thirak re
ladak bhadak banda ho
A man must thrive!
A man must be in charge!
khalak talak banda ho
zikar fikar zinda ho
A man must be concerned!
A man’s pride must be alive and well.
banda ho zinda ho
tabad todak banda ho
A man has to be a warrior!
A man’s thoughts must be as lofty as the sky.
falak talak banda ho
sabar shukar zinda ho
A guy must be patient!
A man’s pride must be alive and well.
banda ho zinda ho
tadpan ranga re
His aspirations must be audible.
His heartbeat must be burning with flames.
dhadkan angare
tann mann ganga re
His heart and body must be as pure as the Ganga.
zinda banda ho
arey tann mann ganga re
His heart and body must be as holy as the Ganga;
these are the hallmarks of a living man.
zinda banda ho
hey!
jhatpat jhoomar ghoomar
The anklet jingles constantly and instantly.
jhanjar baaje re
pairon tale dhuan chale
Fire burns under the feet.
woh na saache jo na naache
One who does not think, does not dance!
ab na rukna chalne de
Don’t stop now, let the song play!
jhatpat jhoomar ghoomar
The anklet jingles incessantly and quickly.
jhanjar baaje re
koyi humare jaisa kahan
Where in the world do people like us exist?
hum na jahan se humse jahan
We don’t belong to the world;
rather, the world belongs to us.
jee mein jashan mein aahat chale
There is a stomping in our hearts and our joys.
apne hunar mein chahat chale
There is a fondness for our skills.
thirak thirak thakna kyun
Why must you get exhausted when dancing?
Why should we be looking around when dancing?
tunak tunak takna kyun
jhijhak jhijhak jhakhna kyun
Why should we be hesitant?
A man must make the most of his life.
banda ho zinda ho
ladak bhadak banda ho
A man has to be a warrior!
A man’s thoughts must be as lofty as the sky.
falak talak banda ho
zikar fikar zinda ho
A man must be concerned!
A man’s pride must be alive and well.
banda ho zinda ho
jeena jaane jo
A living man is one who understands how to live;
one who listens to his heart;
dil ki maane jo
kar de thaane jo
One who does what he chooses.
zinda banda ho
arey kar de thaane jo
A live man is one who carries out his decisions.
zinda banda ho
jhatpat jhoomar ghoomar
The anklet jingles constantly and instantly.
jhanjar baaje re
pairon tale dhuan chale
Fire burns under the feet.
woh na saache jo na naache
One who does not think, does not dance!
ab na rukna chalne de
Don’t stop now, let the song play!
jhatpat jhoomar ghoomar
The anklet jingles incessantly and quickly.
jhanjar baaje re