sasai na dekigoto sae mo
I think even the tiniest things can be special.
tokubetsu datte omou yo
hora ne ima mo kimi no koto
You see? Even now I can’t stop thinking of you.
kangaechau no
suki to kirai kougo ni
If we divine love and hate by picking flower petals,
kazoete yuku uranai
ni bun no
We’ll only have a 50% chance. We’ll can’t move forward like that!
(ichi no)
kakuritsu
(sore ja)
fumidasenai ne
kitto…
I’m sure that means…
ah kono kankei wa aimaimoko tte iu no ka na
Ahh, this relationship—is this what you’d call “ambiguous”?
tsurezure demo I wish I feel my sweet
But even if things are tedious, I still wish to feel my sweet!
daiji ni shinakucha
I’ve gotta cherish what we have!