kakaeteita kioku no hashikko ni
Held onto the edge of memories,
rakugaki shite me o somuketeru hibi datta
Doodling on them, turning my eyes away day after day.
agaiteitai bukiyou na kotoba kari
I wanted to struggle, borrowing clumsy words,
hitorigoto mimi katamukete o totta kimi datta
You listened to my soliloquies and took my hand.
kantan ni wasurete shimaetara ii no ni na
I wish I could easily forget it all,
mune ni toketa yume o sukuitotte
Scooping out the dreams that melted into my heart.
sou nankai mo kanaetai yo tomannai no
I want to fulfill them so many times, I can’t stop.
koko kara hajimetai
I want to start from here.
kitai shitai kidai shita kono omoi nara
I want to have expectations, with these growing feelings,
ayumeru kara
Because I can walk forward.
nankai mo kanaetai yo tomannai no
I want to fulfill them so many times, I can’t stop.
tsumuideku tsuukaten
Weaving through the checkpoints,
mikai no kairo mae o muite sukoshi zutsu
Facing the uncharted sea route, little by little,
susumeru kara
Because I can move forward.
aa~
konna mon ja owaranai
This can’t end just like this,
ato ippo saki e
Just one more step forward.
nankai mo kanaetai yo tomannai no
I want to fulfill them so many times, I can’t stop.
koko kara hajimetai
I want to start from here.
kitai shitai kidai shita kono omoi nara
I want to have expectations, with these growing feelings,
ayumeru kana
Can I walk forward?
nankai mo kanaetai yo tomannai no
I want to fulfill them so many times, I can’t stop.
kagirinai shuuchakuten
An endless terminus,
kitai no ai o koe ni kaete utau made
Until I sing out the expected love,
saki hokoru yo
It will bloom in full glory.
nankai mo nankai mo nanjuukai mo koetai yo
I want to surpass it many, many times, tens of times,
sabireta sekai no hate
To the end of this desolate world,
mae o muite mou ichido dake
Facing forward once more,
susumeru you ni
So I can move forward.