mou chotto dakara
It's just a little more,
kantan janai ne
But it's still not easy.
yametai to naku toki mo
Even when I cry that I want to give up,
shinzou ga iki wo suru
My heart is still breathing.
mou chotto nanoni
Although it's just a little more,
(nanoni...)
(Although...)
konnanja dame da
It was still no good.
(dame da...)
kietai to sakendara
(No good...)
When I cried that I wanted to disappear,
"kanaetai" ni kizuita yo
I realized I wanted that wish to "come true".
mayoikonda bokura ga kanaderu merodii
When we lost our way, the melody we played,
douka douka todoite ite hoshii
Please, please, we want it to reach you.
ippai tarinai toko umeteku youni
In order to have all of the missing places filled.
hikatte hikatte nemuranai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines. Sleepless 25:00.
hagare sou na kokoro ni yume wo utsu toki
When it looks like our hearts are going to break apart, we'll strike a dream into them.
motto motto chikaku ni ite hoshii
More, more, we want to get closer.
ippai tarinai toko umeteku youni
In order to have all of the missing places filled.
hikatte hikatte nemuranai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines. Sleepless 25:00.
light light light light terashite
Light Light Light Light. Illuminate.
light light aishite
Light Light. Love.
(daijoubu)
light light light light bokura wa
(It's okay)
Light Light Light Light. We are.
light light kono mama
Light Light. Like this.
saitei datte iwarete mo
light light light light terashite
Even if it's the worst, like we were told.
Light Light Light Light. Illuminate.
kitto deaeru kara
light light aishite
Surely, because we met,
Light Light. Love.
(daijoubu)
kankeinai yo mou me no mae da
light light light light bokura wa
(It's okay)
It's not important, as it's already right in front of us.
Light Light Light Light. We are.
kitto deaeru kara
light light kono mama
Surely, because we met.
Light Light. Like this.
hikatte hikatte nemuranai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines. Sleepless 25:00.
douyatte mo kesenai
No matter what, I can't erase it.
boku no kokoro wo kodama suru gomennasai
I'm sorry for the lonely echo from my heart.
naraba sorenaraba kienai naraba
So if that's the case and it won't disappear,
nuritsubuseba ii to hirameita
I had an idea that it would be good to draw over it.
kuro kuro sukima ga naku naru youni
So that the black, black crack would disappear,
mienai youni pen to namida hashiraseta
So that they wouldn't be visible, I quickly moved my pen and the tears running down my face.
kakushita iya kakuseta to omotteita
I wanted to hide it, no, I thought I could hide it.
hazu nanoni
wasureta hazu nanoni
I should have done that.
I should have forgotten it.
ito mo kantan ni hiraku nante
It looks so easy to open up like that.
doushite doushite doushite doushite
Why, why, why, why?
kiitatte kotae wa kaettekonai
Despite me asking, the answer never arrives.
zutto yowai mama nyuugeemu
A new game where I'll remain even more weak.
kitto tsudzuiteku batsu geemu
Surely this game of punishment will continue.
korekara dousureba iindarou
From now on, what should I do, I wonder?
arekara sukoshidemo kawareta no?
Since then, have I changed even a little?
fusagikonda bokura wo mazeau hikari
We mixed the light when our mood was down.
nande? nande? bokura wa yowai noni
Why? Why? Even though we're still weak.
zettai deaeru youni hanarenai youni
In order to definitely meet, so that we won't be apart.
hikatta hikatta nemurenai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines. Sleepless 25:00.
mukaiatte kizuita namida no ato de
When we faced each other, we noticed the remains of our tears.
wakatta wakatta bokura ga yowai kara
We understand, we understand. It's because we're weak.
zettai hagurenai youni shitekuretetanda ne
So that we definitely won't lose each other.
hikatta hikatta nemurenai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines. Sleepless 25:00.
mayoikonda bokura ga kanaderu merodii
When we lost our way, the melody we played,
light light light light terashite
Light Light Light Light. Illuminate.
douka douka todoite ite hoshii
light light aishite
Please, please, we want it to reach you.
Light Light. Love.
ippai tarinai toko umeteku youni
(daijoubu)
light light light light bokura wa
In order to have filled all the missing places.
(It's okay)
Light Light Light Light. We are.
hikatte hikatte nemuranai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines, sleepless 25:00.
light light kono mama
Light Light. Like this.
hagare sou na kokoro ni yume wo utsu toki
When it looks like our hearts are going to break apart,
saitei datte iwarete mo
Even if it's the worst, like we were told,
motto motto chikaku ni ite hoshii
chanto deaeta kara
More, more, we want to get closer.
Properly, because we met,
ippai tarinai toko umeteku youni
(daijoubu)
kankeinai yo mou me no mae ni
In order to have all,
(It's okay)
It's not important as it's already right in front of us.
hikatte hikatte nemurenai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines, sleepless 25:00.
chanto kimi ga iru kara
Properly, because you're here.
hikatte hikatte nemuranai nijuugoji
It shines, it shines, sleepless 25:00.