kumo no sukima ni hitosuji sasu hikari
A ray of light shines through a gap in the clouds
mizutamari tobikoeru keikai na suteppu
As I jump over a puddle with a spring in my step
itsumo no machi ga chigatte mieru kyou wa
The all-too-familiar streets look nothing like they did the day before
nani ka hajimaru yokan afureteru
The very sign of a new beginning
mune ni
shimatta mama no ansaa o tokihanatsu yo kyou
In my heart
Trapped within me this answer, let the chains around it fall
koko kara sekaijuu e ookii yume
Out into the world never before seen, such a big dream
(hey)
issho ni kanae ni ikou te o tsunaide ano kado no mukou
We’ll make it come true, hand in hand, beyond that corner in the wall
(kou)
itsumo doori no keshiki kaeru reshipi mitsukerareta yo
Always the same scenery, changing with this recipe, right here in front of us all
kimi ga ite kureru nara
As long as you’re here with me
umaku ikisouna ki ga suru yo
Somehow, I feel like nothing can go wrong
yumemita ano basho made kakenukeyou
So let’s charge right at the place of our dreams!
oso sugiru nante nai
It’s never too late to start
fukanou nante nai
Nothing’s ever impossible to achieve
itsudatte omoi tattara sono hi ga hajimari no Day1
The day you decide to make a move will always be your very own Day 1
minareta keshiki o
To change the sights we’re so used to seeing
kaeteku sutaato rain
We’re now standing at the start line
iroasenai bokura no sutoorii o
Let’s start writing our very own story
issho ni ima hajimeyou
That’ll never ever fade away
kurikaeshi no ruutin ni iro o tsukeru myuujikku
Your unchanging everyday routine, giving it vibrant colors, our music
bokura dake ga wakaru aizu awasete iku chuuningu
The sign only visible to our eyes, go along with it, time for a tuning
yuiitsu mu ni sorezore kawari nante inai
You and me, we’re one and only, can’t change us for anyone else
(nai)
kawari bae shinai ima kaete kitai
Can’t change me for anyone else, but it’s now time for a change!
(nai)
motto wakuwaku shitetai
I wanna get even more excited
motto dokidoki shite itai yo
To make my heart beat faster than ever before
taikutsu na mainichi o nurikaechaou
So let’s give our mundane everyday a fresh new coat of paint!
taka sugiru nante nai
Nothing’s ever too high up
enryo wa mou shinai
There’s no longer a need to hold back
kono ashi de yuuki o dashite dokomademo tobiagacchaou
With my own two feet, I’ll gather my courage, and fly high beyond the sky
nigiri kaesu te no tsuyosa ga messeeji
The strength of your grip is the clearest message
hitori janai yo minna de
That I’m not alone, together with everyone
atarashii monogatari o hajimeyou
Let our very own story begin
tsuyoku te o tsunaide
Holding your hand tight in mine
takai kabe mo norikoeru
We’ll scale the walls before us together
hitori ja mirenai keshiki
To see the sights we never could have alone
minna nara mireru kara
The sights that we could only see together
mune no takanaru oto ga sutaato no aizu
The sound of our hearts beating is the sign of a new start
oso sugiru nante nai
It’s never too late to start
fukanou nante nai
Nothing’s ever impossible to achieve
itsudatte omoi tattara sono hi ga hajimari no Day1
The day you decide to make a move will always be your very own Day 1
minareta keshiki o
To change the sights we’re so used to seeing
kaeteku sutaato rain
We’re now standing at the start line
iroasenai bokura no sutoorii o
Let’s start writing our very own story
issho ni ima hajimeyou
That’ll never ever fade away